<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>留学生CS编程作业代写</title>
  
  <subtitle>专业 高效 原创 QQ：1926742804</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/"/>
  <updated>2022-10-04T04:41:55.919Z</updated>
  <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>CPlusPlus小砖家</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS20-Karatsuba-Algorithm</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS20-Karatsuba-Algorithm.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS20-Karatsuba-Algorithm.html</id>
    <published>2022-10-04T04:40:21.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-10-04T04:41:55.919Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Task-Description"><a href="#Task-Description" class="headerlink" title="Task Description"></a>Task Description</h3><p>You should carry out this work as a group of 2 students. You should work together but each student has to do their own submission to the websubmission system and marks will be automatically allocated individually.<br>You are asked to use C++ to implement</p><ul><li>School Method for Integer Addition</li><li>Karatsuba Algorithm for Integer Multiplication</li></ul><h3 id="Submission-Guideline"><a href="#Submission-Guideline" class="headerlink" title="Submission Guideline"></a>Submission Guideline</h3><p>You must follow this guideline! Your submission will be marked automatically. Failure to follow this guideline will result in 0.<br>Your submission should contain exactly one file: main.cpp. You do not need to submit a design.</p><p>Your program takes one line as input. The input line contains three integers separated by spaces. Let the three integers be “I1 I2 B”. I1 and I2 are both nonnegative integers up to 100 digits long. B represents I1 and I2’s base (B is from 2 to 10).</p><p>Your program should output the sum of I1 and I2, using the school method, then the product of I1 and I2, using the Karatsuba algorithm. The results should still use base B. Please separate the results using one space.<br><figure class="highlight yaml"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="attr">Sample input 1:</span> <span class="number">101</span> <span class="number">5</span> <span class="number">10</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="attr">Sample output 1:</span> <span class="number">106</span> <span class="number">505</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="attr">Sample input 2:</span> <span class="number">10</span> <span class="number">111</span> <span class="number">2</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="attr">Sample output 2:</span> <span class="number">1001</span> <span class="number">1110</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><h3 id="Marking"><a href="#Marking" class="headerlink" title="Marking"></a>Marking</h3><p>Marking will be done automatically. We trust that you’d indeed implement the school method for addition and the Karatsuba algorithm for multiplication. We will randomly pick some submissions to verify whether it is the case. If you use other methods in your submission, it will be considered cheating and you will receive 0.</p><p>Submit to Websubmission before the above deadline. The websubmission system for this assignment will be open on 6 August. Websubmission will run an automatic testing script immediately after each submission. Your mark is simply the fraction of test cases that you pass. E.g., if there are 100 test cases, and your code passes 78 of them, then your mark is 78/100. You can submit as many times as you want. The last submission before the deadline will be your “official” submission.</p><h3 id="SVN-Instructions"><a href="#SVN-Instructions" class="headerlink" title="SVN Instructions"></a>SVN Instructions</h3><p>First of all, you need to create a directory under version control.<br>To check out a working copy, type svn checkout.</p><p>SVN helps keeping track of file changes (over different commits). You should commit your work early and often.</p><h3 id="Websubmission"><a href="#Websubmission" class="headerlink" title="Websubmission"></a>Websubmission</h3><p>You are asked to submit via the web interface. The submission steps should be self-explanatory. Simply choose the correct semester, course, and assignment. The websubmission system will automatically fetch the latest version of your work from your SVN repository (you may also choose to submit older versions). Once your work is submitted, the system will launch a script checking the format of your submission. Click “View Feedback” to view the results. You are welcome to resubmit for as many times as you wish (before the deadline).</p><p>We will compile your code using g++ -o main.out -O2 -Wall main.cpp. It is your responsibility to ensure that your code compiles on the university system.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      使用C++完成Karatsuba Algorithm算法的实现。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Algorithm" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Algorithm/"/>
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>DSA2020-Zombie-Simulator</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/DSA2020-Zombie-Simulator.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/DSA2020-Zombie-Simulator.html</id>
    <published>2022-10-01T11:34:07.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-10-01T11:35:34.075Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Question-1-Zombie-Simulator-recommended-readings-1-3-1-4"><a href="#Question-1-Zombie-Simulator-recommended-readings-1-3-1-4" class="headerlink" title="Question 1 - Zombie Simulator (recommended readings 1.3, 1.4)"></a>Question 1 - Zombie Simulator (recommended readings 1.3, 1.4)</h3><p>Using the UML below, create a class called Human which represents a human being whom can walk around a simulated world.<br><figure class="highlight vala"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br><span class="line">8</span><br><span class="line">9</span><br><span class="line">10</span><br><span class="line">11</span><br><span class="line">12</span><br><span class="line">13</span><br><span class="line">14</span><br><span class="line">15</span><br><span class="line">16</span><br><span class="line">17</span><br><span class="line">18</span><br><span class="line">19</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">Human</span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># x,y : double</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># dx,dy : double</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># size : double</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># isAlive : boolean</span></span><br><span class="line">+ world_width, world_height : <span class="keyword">int</span></span><br><span class="line">---------------------------------</span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># max_speed : double</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># sightDistance : int</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># generator : Random</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta"># others : List&lt;Human&gt;</span></span><br><span class="line">---------------------------------</span><br><span class="line">+ Human(others:List&lt;Human&gt;, x:<span class="keyword">double</span>, y:<span class="keyword">double</span>)</span><br><span class="line">+ run(): <span class="keyword">void</span></span><br><span class="line">+ getX(): <span class="keyword">double</span></span><br><span class="line">+ getY(): <span class="keyword">double</span></span><br><span class="line">+ getSize() : <span class="keyword">double</span></span><br><span class="line">+ kill() : <span class="keyword">void</span></span><br><span class="line">+ draw(g : Graphics) : <span class="keyword">void</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>Each Human can run as a separate thread and maintains an x,y position with periodic movements using dx, dy which change slightly after a number of iterations. A Human can be instantiated using an initial position and a list of all other humans in the world. A Human can be drawn using the draw method and passing a Graphics object around its x,y position and size. There are also a static public fields which can be set to determine the size of the world in which humans roam.</p><p>Create a Zombie class which extends a Human. Try to work out what Human fields/methods should be overridden. A Zombie has a sight distance of the entire panel and will actively seek and search out the nearest human, it will then alter its dx,dy movements towards the closest human for a fixed period of time before checking if there is any other targets it could possibly chase. A Zombie can only move half of the max speed as a human. If a Zombie manages to catch a human it will bite and kill the human.</p><p>Modify the human class so that it tries to move away from the closest zombie within its sight distance by modifying its dx,dy speed. A Human sight distance is only of the world size.</p><p>Create a GUI called ZombieSimulator with two buttons, starting either a zombie or a human as a thread. The GUI should periodically redraw all Human and Zombie objects moving within the world. It should maintain a single thread safe data structure for all Zombie and Human objects. It should also periodically check if a human has been killed by a zombie, in which case it re-instantiates the object as a new Zombie thread. See below for an example screenshot, where zombies are red squares and humans’ blue circles.</p><p>Feel free to add any private/protected helper methods across any of the classes which you feel would improve the design of your program and play with any of the formula constants (eg sight distance, max speed, sleep time) to improve the feel of the simulator.</p><h3 id="Question-2-Skip-List-Set-recommended-readings-2-2"><a href="#Question-2-Skip-List-Set-recommended-readings-2-2" class="headerlink" title="Question 2 - Skip List Set (recommended readings 2.2)"></a>Question 2 - Skip List Set (recommended readings 2.2)</h3><p>A skip list data structure is a modification of a singly linked list so that the add, contains, and remove methods are O(log2 n). Essentially it consists of a series of singly-linked lists L0, L1, …, Lk, usually visualized one on top of another with L0 at the bottom. The list L0 holds all the (nonnull) elements of the collection in order with null at the start and end of the list. Each list Li+1 holds a subset of the previous list Li and has links from each element down to the same element in the previous list. These links enable elements in the collection to be found more efficiently than by just traversing the list L0. The illustrated skip list holds three elements e0, e1, e2 in comparable order:</p><p>When an element is added to the skip list it is first randomly decided in how many of the lists it will appear (it is always placed in the list L0, and if in a list Li it has a 50-50 chance of also being in Li+1 and so on). Then the correct insertion place is found in the topmost list to which it will be added (which might result in a new top list being created), and then working downward it is added to each of the lists below. An element is found by starting at the top list (referenced by firstNode), following the next links until either the element is found, the end of the list would be reached, or else the element would be passed. If not yet found, a down link is followed to continue the process with the list below. To remove an element the element should be removed from each list in which it appears (starting with the topmost list).</p><p>Using the UML below as a guide, prepare a class called SkipListSet that extends AbstractSet (and so implements the Set interface) using a skip list data structure and the following UML diagram as a guide. Include a suitable main method which effectively tests your skip list implementation.</p><p>A screenshot of an example test is shown below, note that for convenience and debugging purposes the skip list toString prints all node elements on each level.</p><h3 id="Question-3-Deque-implementations-recommended-readings-3-3"><a href="#Question-3-Deque-implementations-recommended-readings-3-3" class="headerlink" title="Question 3 - Deque implementations (recommended readings: 3.3)"></a>Question 3 - Deque implementations (recommended readings: 3.3)</h3><p>A deque (pronounced deck) or double-ended queue, is a linear collection that allows insertion and removal at both ends. The interface above called DequeADT, available from Blackboard, is an abstract data type which can hold any generic element E, it also describes operations for a deque.</p><p>Create two data structure implementations of the Deque, one which uses an underlying array called ArrayDeque and one which uses an underlying dynamic doubly-linked structure called DoublyLinkedDeque. Implement the deque data structures yourself, do not use extra Java Collection classes!</p><p>For efficiency first, last, enqueueRear, enqueueFront, dequeueRear, dequeueFront, clear, size, and isEmpty should all be O(1) operations. Feel free to add any necessary private helper methods and a suitable toString which returns a string representation for your deque implementation.</p><p>Further enhance your classes to make sure all methods are safe from unexpected events using appropriate exception handling (example, if user code tries to remove something from the deque when empty, it should throw an appropriate exception). Create a test class with a suitable main method which effectively tests all operations on one or both deque implementations.</p><p>See the screenshot below for an example of testing one of the deque implementations.</p><h3 id="Question-4-Bitwise-Radix-Sort-recommended-readings-3-5-3-6"><a href="#Question-4-Bitwise-Radix-Sort-recommended-readings-3-5-3-6" class="headerlink" title="Question 4 - Bitwise Radix Sort (recommended readings 3.5, 3.6)"></a>Question 4 - Bitwise Radix Sort (recommended readings 3.5, 3.6)</h3><p>Radix sort is a sorting algorithm that focuses on sorting parts that comprise the number rather than the whole number directly. Usually it can only be used on fixed digit or character inputs such as post codes or county codes. Radix sort focusses on each digit/char at a time and placing it in a desired queue shared with other parts of the same value. After all elements are queued, it polls all elements back into an original list. It repeats this process k times where k is the amount of digits/chars that comprise the element. However, if we had to sort a single digit element across a larger range of possibilities (eg Ascii or Unicode values) then a different strategy for radix sort can be utilised at a bit level, instead focussing on the bits which make up the data type.</p><p>Create a simple static method called bitwiseRadixSort which takes a char[] of Unicode values and sorts them looking at the individual bits which form each char data type. Include a main method to test using randomly generated char values as demonstrated with the screenshot below. Note it may be beneficial to print out the Unicode number as well as the printed char so that you know your sort is working.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      完成数据结构作业，包括Zombie Simulator, Skip List Set, Deque以及Redix Sort, 量比较大。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Java" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/Java/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Data Structure" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Data-Structure/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>COMP20003-K-D-Trees</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMP20003-K-D-Trees.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMP20003-K-D-Trees.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-28T02:08:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-28T02:10:30.922Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Purpose"><a href="#Purpose" class="headerlink" title="Purpose"></a>Purpose</h3><p>The purpose of this assignment is for you to:</p><p>Increase your proficiency in C programming, your dexterity with dynamic memory allocation and your understanding of more advanced data structures (K-D trees).<br>Increase your understanding of how computational complexity can affect the performance of an algorithm by conducting orderly experiments with your program and comparing the results of your experimentation with theory.<br>Increase your proficiency in using UNIX utilities.</p><h3 id="Background"><a href="#Background" class="headerlink" title="Background"></a>Background</h3><p>Interactive navigation tools like Google Maps and GPS navigation systems are commonplace, but how do these systems actually work? Spatial datasets can be very large: OpenStreetMap, an opensource global mapping dataset, contains over 10 million points of interest. Various algorithms and data structures have been developed to allow users to quickly search and navigate these large spatial datasets.</p><h3 id="Your-task"><a href="#Your-task" class="headerlink" title="Your task"></a>Your task</h3><p>In this assignment, you will create a K-D tree to support interactive map functionality for the City of Melbourne Census of Land Use and Employment (CLUE) dataset. A user will be able to query locations to find nearby businesses.</p><p>In Assignment 1, you wrote code to read the census data from a file, insert the records as nodes in a linked list, and allow users to search for records by trading name. In this assignment, you should modify your code to insert records into a K-D tree and allow users to search by x,y coordinates. You can use your own Assignment 1 code for this assignment or the sample solution we have provided.</p><h3 id="Dataset"><a href="#Dataset" class="headerlink" title="Dataset"></a>Dataset</h3><p>This assignment uses the same dataset as Assignment 1, which is a subset of the Business Establishment Trading Name and Industry Classification 2018 dataset, accessed from: <a href="https://data.melbourne.vic.gov.au/Business/Business-establishment-trading-nameand-industry-c/vesm-c7r2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://data.melbourne.vic.gov.au/Business/Business-establishment-trading-nameand-industry-c/vesm-c7r2</a></p><p>The x coordinate and y coordinate columns should be used as the 2-D key to store and query records. The other columns can be treated as the associated data.</p><h3 id="Deliverable-1-Source-code"><a href="#Deliverable-1-Source-code" class="headerlink" title="Deliverable 1 - Source code"></a>Deliverable 1 - Source code</h3><p>Stage 1 - What’s here?<br>In stage 1, you will implement the basic functionality for an interactive map that allows a user to click on locations and retrieve data about the nearest point of interest. Instead of clicks, your code will accept (x,y) pairs from stdin, find the closest business establishment to that location in the dataset, and output the information about that establishment to a file.</p><p>Your Makefile should produce an executable program called map1. This program should take two command line arguments: (1) the name of the data file used to build the tree, and (2) the name of an output file.</p><p>Your map1 program should:</p><p>Construct a K-D tree to store the information contained in the data file specified in the command line argument. Each record (row) should be stored in a separate Node.<br>Handle duplicates (businesses located at exactly the same x,y coordinates) by chaining them together in a linked list connected to a single Node in the K-D tree. Exact duplicate locations should not be added as separate Nodes in the tree.<br>Accept locations queries from stdin and search the tree for the location nearest to the query point. The record(s) of the business(s) at this location should be printed to the output file. If there are multiple businesses at this location, all of them must be included in the output.<br>In addition to outputting the record(s) to the output file, the number of key comparisons performed during the search should be written to stdout.<br>For testing, it may be convenient to create a file of keys to be searched, one per line, and redirect the input from this file. Use the UNIX operator &lt; to redirect input from a file.</p><p>Example input<br>map1 datafile outputfile then type in queries; or<br>map1 datafile outputfile &lt; queryfile<br>Queries should be entered as x,y pairs separated by a space: x y</p><p>Example output<br>Note that the key is output to both the file and to stdout, for identification purposes. Also note that the number of comparisons is only output at the end of the search, so there is only one number for key comparisons per key, even when multiple records have been located for that key.</p><p>The format need not be exactly as above; variations in whitespace/tabs are permitted. The number of comparisons above has been made up, do not take it as an example of a correct execution!</p><h3 id="Stage-2-Radius-search"><a href="#Stage-2-Radius-search" class="headerlink" title="Stage 2 - Radius search"></a>Stage 2 - Radius search</h3><p>In stage 2, you will code a function that allows the user to find all of the business establishments within some distance of a query point. Your code will accept (x,y,radius) triplets from stdin, find all business establishments within the requested radius of the x,y point, and output the information about those establishments to a file.</p><p>Your Makefile should produce an executable program called map2. This program should take two command line arguments: (1) the name of the data file used to build the tree, and (2) the name of an output file.</p><p>Your map2 program should:<br>Construct a K-D tree to store the information contained in the data file specified in the command line argument, exactly as in Stage 1. Note that you can (and should!) reuse your code from Stage 1 to do this step.<br>Accept x,y,radius queries from stdin and search the tree for all locations within the requested radius of the x,y point. These records should be printed to the output file. When there are multiple businesses at the same location, all of these records should be included in the output.<br>If no business establishments are located with the query radius, your code must output the word NOTFOUND.<br>In addition to outputting the above data to the output file, the number of key comparisons performed during the search should be written to stdout.</p><h4 id="Example-input"><a href="#Example-input" class="headerlink" title="Example input"></a>Example input</h4><p>map2 datafile outputfile then type in queries; or<br>map2 datafile outputfile &lt; queryfile<br>Queries should be entered as x,y,radius triplets separated by spaces: x y r</p><p>Example output<br>Note that the key is output to both the file and to stdout, for identification purposes. Also note that the number of comparisons is only output at the end of the search, so there is only one number for key comparisons per key, even when multiple records have been located for that key.</p><p>The format need not be exactly as above; variations in whitespace/tabs are permitted. The number of comparisons above has been made up, do not take it as an example of a correct execution!</p><h3 id="Programming-Style"><a href="#Programming-Style" class="headerlink" title="Programming Style"></a>Programming Style</h3><p>Programming style will be assessed as in Assignment 1 and is worth 2 marks.</p><h3 id="Deliverable-2-Experimentation"><a href="#Deliverable-2-Experimentation" class="headerlink" title="Deliverable 2 - Experimentation"></a>Deliverable 2 - Experimentation</h3><p>You will run various files through your program to test its accuracy and also to examine the number of key comparisons used when searching. We have provided a few different versions of the .csv file that can be used to build the tree. You should test your code with a variety of inputs and report on the number of key comparisons used by your code in Stage 1 and Stage 2. You will compare these results with each other and, importantly with what you expected based on theory (big-O).</p><p>Your experimentation should be systematic, varying the size and characteristics of the files you use (e.g. sorted or random), and observing how the number of key comparisons varies. Repeating a test case with different keys and taking the average can be useful.</p><p>Some useful UNIX commands for creating test files with different characteristics include sort, sort -R (man sort for more information on the -R option), and shuf. You can randomize your input data and pick the first x keys as the lookup keywords.</p><p>If you use only keyboard input for searches, it is unlikely that you will be able to generate enough data to analyze your results. You should familiarize yourself with the powerful UNIX facilities for redirecting standard input (stdin) and standard output (stdout). You might also find it useful to familiarize yourself with UNIX pipes ‘|’ and possibly also the UNIX program awk for processing structured output. For example, if you pipe your output into echo ‘’abc:def’’ | awk -F ‘:’ ‘{print $1}’, you will output only the first column (abc). In the example, -F specifies the delimiter. Instead of using echo you can use cat filename.csv | awk -F ‘;’ ‘{print $1}’ which will print only the first column of the filename.csv file. You can build up a file of numbers of key comparisons using the shell append operator &gt;&gt;, e.x. your command &gt;&gt; file to append to.</p><p>You will write up your findings and submit this report separately from your code. You should present your findings clearly, in light of what you know about the data structures used in your programs and their known computational complexity. Tables and/or graphs are recommended for presenting numeric results. You may find that your results are what you expected, based on theory. Alternatively, you may find your results do not agree with theory. In either case, you should state what you expected from the theory, and if there is a discrepancy you should suggest possible reasons.</p><h3 id="Notes-on-K-D-Trees"><a href="#Notes-on-K-D-Trees" class="headerlink" title="Notes on K-D Trees"></a>Notes on K-D Trees</h3><p>K-D trees are an extension of binary search trees for k-dimensional keys. When searching, each layer of the tree checks a different dimension of the key. In the 2-D case, the root of the tree should consider only the first element of the key (x) and split left or right depending on whether the first element of the search key is less than or greater than the first element of the root’s key. The second layer of nodes should consider only the second element of the key (y). The third layer should consider the first element, etc. To illustrate, consider how the key (6, 0) would be inserted into the K-D tree shown below.</p><p>The root node compares the first elements of the keys and since 6 &gt; 3, it directs the search right. The next node compares the second elements of the keys and since 0 &lt; 2, it directs the search left. The new node (6, 0) is then inserted as a left child.</p><p>Note that it is possible for a key to match an existing node on either x or y but not both. These partial matches are not duplicates and should be inserted as new nodes in the tree. For example, suppose the next node inserted was (2, 8). This would go left from the root because 2 &lt; 3 and be compared to (1, 8). The second element of the keys match: 8 = 8, but the keys are not exactly the same (2, 8) = (1, 8). So (2, 8) could be inserted as either a left or right child of (1, 8) (for consistency with our testing code, please put equal value keys to the right).</p><h4 id="Searching-for-the-nearest-point-to-a-query"><a href="#Searching-for-the-nearest-point-to-a-query" class="headerlink" title="Searching for the nearest point to a query"></a>Searching for the nearest point to a query</h4><p>To find the nearest node to a query point, you will need to search through the tree, keeping track of the closest match found so far, and the squared distance d to that closest match. Start at the root of thepK-D tree. At each node, check the distance between the current node and the query location. If this distance is lower than the current d, replace the current “closest” match with the current node and set d = D. Then compare the current node’s key to the query. (As in insertion, only one element of the node’s key should be compared to the query - for example, at the root node, compare x values only, and in the first layer nodes compare y values only.) Proceed down one or both branches of the tree depending on the distance between the current node’s key and the query:<br>If the current node’s key is &gt; d from the query, proceed down either the left or right branch of the tree depending on whether the query is less or greater than the current node’s key.<br>If the current node’s key is &lt;= d from the query, proceed down both branches of the tree.<br>These two cases are illustrated in the images below. In this example, M is a node of the K-D tree which splits the data along the x dimension (indicated by the black line) and Q is the query location. d is the distance to the current “closest” match. In the first case (a), the x distance between M and Q is larger than d, so no points left of M could be closer to Q than the current “closest” match. There is no need to search the left children of M . In the second case, the x distance between M and Q is less than d, so there is a chance that there could be a point left of M that is closer than the current match. In order to guarantee that we find the closest possible point to Q, it is necessary to search both the left and right children of M .</p><h4 id="Searching-for-points-in-a-radius"><a href="#Searching-for-points-in-a-radius" class="headerlink" title="Searching for points in a radius"></a>Searching for points in a radius</h4><p>Searching for points within a radius of a query is similar to searching for the nearest point. Start at the root of the K-D tree, and at each node, check the distance between the current node and the query location. If this distance is within the requested radius, output the information related to this node and proceed down both branches to look for further matches. If the current node is outside the requested radius, check the distance between the current node’s key and the query coordinates as above, and proceed down the left, right, or both branches of the tree accordingly.</p><h4 id="Conventions-and-recommendations"><a href="#Conventions-and-recommendations" class="headerlink" title="Conventions and recommendations"></a>Conventions and recommendations</h4><p>For easier testing and debugging, we ask that you follow these conventions:</p><p>The root of the tree should check the x coordinate of the key.<br>Equal keys (meaning, keys that match the current node on the portion of the key it checks, but differ from the current node on the other value) should be grouped with the keys greater than the current node, so each node splits keys into values &lt; and &gt;= the node’s key.<br>The x and y coordinates should be stored as double type.</p><p>Math functions like sqrt() and pow() can be found in the &lt;math.h&gt; library.</p><p>Until you are confident your code is working, you might want to test the radius search function with small radius values (e.g., around 0.0005).</p><h3 id="Additional-Support"><a href="#Additional-Support" class="headerlink" title="Additional Support"></a>Additional Support</h3><p>Your tutors will be available to help with your assignment during the scheduled workshop times. Questions related to the assignment may be posted on the Piazza forum, using the folder tag assignment1 for new posts. You should feel free to answer other students’ questions if you are confident of your skills.</p><p>A tutor will check the Discussion Forum regularly, and answer some questions, but be aware that for some questions you will just need to use your judgment and document your thinking. For example, a question like, “How much data should I use for the experiments?”, will not be answered; you must try out different data and see what makes sense.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      实现K-D Tree, 使用并完成一个类似Google Map的应用程序。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS210-Word-Search</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS210-Word-Search.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS210-Word-Search.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-25T03:19:59.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-25T03:22:16.649Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Description"><a href="#Description" class="headerlink" title="Description"></a>Description</h3><p>Since words were etched in stone, people have loved to do word searches. The game is to search for words in a grid of letters. As you may know, it can be difficult to find every single word in the grid though. So let’s write a program to do just that!</p><p>Your task is to read in a file representing a grid of characters and a file representing a dictionary of valid words. You will then search through the grid of letters to find all the valid words in the grid.</p><p>Important details to note:</p><p>Our program will only search in the vertical and horizontal directions. Do not search for words in the diagonal direction.<br>Our grids can be any size. The file specifying the grid will have a number as its first line which represents the number of rows, and another number as the second line representing the number of columns. See the example file below. You are guaranteed that both the number of rows and the number of columns will always to 4.<br>If a word exists in a grid multiple times, print it out each time you find it.<br>A word is a valid word if</p><p>It is at least three letters long.<br>It can be formed from letters in the grid that are adjacent along a row (left-to-right or right-to-left) or along a column (top-to-bottom or bottom-to-top). Note we are not worrying about diagonal words in this assignment.<br>It can be found in the dictionary file.</p><h3 id="Expected-Behavior"><a href="#Expected-Behavior" class="headerlink" title="Expected Behavior"></a>Expected Behavior</h3><p>Read in the dictionary file and the file specifying the grid of letters. The names of these files will be in command-line arguments 0 and 1 respectively. The dictionary file name will be in args[0] and the filename specifying the grid will be in args1. For examples discussing command-line arguments see the class examples on github here.<br>Read the dictionary file into a Java collection. You will use this collection to check if a word found in the grid is a valid word or not. What data structure makes sense here?<br>Read the grid file to create a grid of strings. You know exactly how many rows and columns your grid has before creating it. What data structure makes sense here? Remember that Java collections can store other collections. So you can have a list of lists or a set of sets or an array of arrays for instance.<br>Search your grid to find valid words. Matching words from the grid to the dictionary file should be done case-insensitive. i.e. if there exists a word Abe in the dictionary, a sequence of letters in the grid “a”, “b”, “e” should match that word.<br>Collect the legal words found into a list and print them out as indicated below. The order in which you print them matters.</p><h3 id="Examples"><a href="#Examples" class="headerlink" title="Examples"></a>Examples</h3><p>The following is an example of the grid of letters file:<br><figure class="highlight stylus"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br><span class="line">8</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="number">6</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="number">6</span></span><br><span class="line">y h l l w p</span><br><span class="line">c s <span class="selector-tag">p</span> o o l</span><br><span class="line">o e h <span class="selector-tag">b</span> <span class="selector-tag">b</span> y</span><br><span class="line">d y <span class="selector-tag">b</span> w <span class="selector-tag">a</span> y</span><br><span class="line">e <span class="selector-tag">p</span> w x <span class="selector-tag">a</span> c</span><br><span class="line">j k <span class="selector-tag">a</span> z <span class="selector-tag">i</span> g</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>In this example, you know you have 6 rows (from the first line) and 6 columns (from the second line). You would then read in the grid. Note that in general the input grid could have a mix of uppercase or lowercase letters. For this grid, and the dictionary.txt included in the starter code, your program would find the below words:<br>cod, code, ode, ply (horizontal, L-to-R)<br>jed, doc, yes, abo, bow (horizontal, R-to-L)<br>spool, pool, way (vertical, top-to-bottom)<br>loop, loops (vertical, bottom-to-top)</p><p>View the dictionary.txt file in the starter code to see an example of this type of file. Note your program should not print the ‘(horizontal, L-to-R)’ part. It should only print the words one per line in the same order as above though. So the expected output for the above example would be:</p><h3 id="Input-Files"><a href="#Input-Files" class="headerlink" title="Input Files"></a>Input Files</h3><p>We have provided sample input files for you to test your program in the starter code. It is important to note though that you should test your program on lots of other files. We certainly will.</p><h3 id="Tips-and-Hints"><a href="#Tips-and-Hints" class="headerlink" title="Tips and Hints"></a>Tips and Hints</h3><p>You will certainly need to think carefully about the strategy for checking for words in a row or column of the grid. And this strategy must output words in the same order that we expect them. Start by thinking about searching from left to right. Consider the first row:</p><p>Notice that this row contains the words cod, code, and ode. Suppose that the row is represented as the array [“y”, “c”, “o”, “d”, “e”, “j”]. A simple way to explore all the possible words (going L to R) in this list would be as follows (the process for the other rows is similar).</p><p>Starting at the first element (i.e., “y”), check whether the sequence of length 3 starting at that position is a legal word (we start with length 3 because a legal word has to be at least three letters long). Then check for length 4, then for length 5, etc., until you reach the end of the list.<br>Now repeat this step, but starting at the second element (i.e., “c”). Notice that this time you will come to the end of the list one step sooner. Then repeat for the third element, and so on.</p><p>Note that the above process can be made easier by first converting the array of individual letters into one concatenated string. This could also lead to some great reuse of code. Then for all different types of searches you would produce a string representing that sequence of characters that you want to search and you can use one function to check a sequence for any valid words.</p><p>Everyone solves problems differently, but I thought it would be helpful to highlight a few functions I used in case you find them helpful as well.</p><p>str.toLowerCase()<br>Integer.valueOf(…). When reading in the number of rows and columns, I recommend using Integer.valueOf(scanner.nextLine()) instead of trying to use scanner.nextInt().<br>str.split(…)<br>str.charAt(…)<br>str.substring(…, …)</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      完成游戏Word Search的实现。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
      <category term="Game" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Game/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CSCI1200-Crossword-Checker</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CSCI1200-Crossword-Checker.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CSCI1200-Crossword-Checker.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-22T14:34:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-22T14:37:06.213Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>In this homework you will work with command line arguments, file input and output, and the C++ STL string and vector classes to check the words in a class crossword puzzle board. Please read the entire handout for the assignment before starting to program. In addition to the lecture notes, you will also want to refer to the “Helpful C++ Programming Information” and “Good Programming Practices” sections of the course webpage.</p><p>Here’s a very small example of a classic crossword puzzle. The board consists of a grid of squares with some of the squares blacked out. The remaining white squares need to be filled with 1 letter per square forming words of 2 or more letters that run in the horizontal (left to right) and vertical (top to bottom) directions. The traditional crossword puzzle provides clues/definitions for each of these words. Each white square that is the first letter of one or more words is numbered. White squares that are the middle or end of words are not numbered. Can you solve this crossword puzzle by hand?</p><p>Your task for this assignment is to write a tool to help confirm that a filled in crossword puzzle contains real English words by picking out the letters from the board and checking them against a list of allowed words. This tool could be useful both to crossword puzzle solvers and also to crossword puzzle designers.</p><p>NOTE: We will not be tackling the much harder problem of matching words to clues or generating clues for words, which would requires a large vocabulary, clever use of puns, knowledge of pop culture, etc. and is an active area of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Natural Language Processing (NLP) research.</p><h3 id="Command-Line-Arguments"><a href="#Command-Line-Arguments" class="headerlink" title="Command Line Arguments"></a>Command Line Arguments</h3><p>To check the validity of a filled-in crossword puzzle board, your program will expect two required arguments and one optional argument. The first argument is the puzzle filename containing the grid of characters in the proposed board. The second argument is the dictionary filename containing all of the allowed words. If provided, the third argument will specify how to display the puzzle using ASCII art. Here are a few example command lines:<br><figure class="highlight stylus"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">./crossword_checker<span class="selector-class">.out</span> puzzle6<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> linux_dict_words.txt</span><br><span class="line">./crossword_checker<span class="selector-class">.out</span> puzzle6<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> linux_dict_words<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> --print</span><br><span class="line">./crossword_checker<span class="selector-class">.out</span> puzzle6<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> linux_dict_words<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> --print_coordinates</span><br><span class="line">./crossword_checker<span class="selector-class">.out</span> puzzle6<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> linux_dict_words<span class="selector-class">.txt</span> --print_numbered</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>You must exactly follow the specifications for the command line and output to ensure you receive full credit for your work. We provide sample input and output files on the course website, and the automated testing and autograding on Submitty will also help you check your work. We recommend starting with the lower numbered puzzles first, and working to higher numbered puzzles as you debug your work.</p><p>The file puzzle6.txt contains the filled-in crossword puzzle for the example above. The black squares of the board are represented with the number character, ‘#’.<br><figure class="highlight clean"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">a##b</span><br><span class="line">pale</span><br><span class="line">e#ad</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>The file of allowed words used in the example command lines is the contents of the Ubuntu Linux American English dictionary - a version of this file may already be on your computer in /usr/share/dict/words. This file is simple plaintext with one word per line. You are encouraged to copy and add or remove words from this file or create a new file with alternate words as you test your program. Note that the allowed words file may contain words with lowercase and uppercase letters. Crossword puzzles are usually case insensitive, so your program should ignore capitalization when checking if a word is on the accepted list. The allowed words file may include words containing punctuation characters - you should ignore those words.</p><h3 id="Note-on-Error-Checking"><a href="#Note-on-Error-Checking" class="headerlink" title="Note on Error Checking"></a>Note on Error Checking</h3><p>You should implement simple error checking to ensure that the arguments provided are appropriate. You should also check to make sure that the files exist and your program can successfully open and read the contents. Your program should exit gracefully with a useful error message sent to std::cerr, Standard Error (STDERR), if there is a problem with the arguments or the filenames.</p><h3 id="Note-on-Viewing-ASCII-Art-amp-Plaintext-Files"><a href="#Note-on-Viewing-ASCII-Art-amp-Plaintext-Files" class="headerlink" title="Note on Viewing ASCII Art &amp; Plaintext Files"></a>Note on Viewing ASCII Art &amp; Plaintext Files</h3><p>Make sure you’re using a good file viewer/editor to look at these files. It should correctly display the UNIX/GNU Linux ‘\n’ line ending. Use one of the “Plaintext &amp; Code Viewers/Editors” listed on the “C++ Development” page. Don’t attempt use the Windows line ending character ‘\m’ or ‘\r’ because this will fail validation tests on Submitty</p><h3 id="Basic-Output"><a href="#Basic-Output" class="headerlink" title="Basic Output"></a>Basic Output</h3><p>If all of the horizontal or vertical sequences of 2 or more contiguous white box letters are present in the acceptable words file and the optional third argument is not provided, then your program should print this simple success message to std::cout, Standard Output (STDOUT):<br><figure class="highlight ebnf"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="attribute">valid crossword puzzle</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>If one or more of the letter sequences is not present in the acceptable words file, then your program should print all of those non-words to std::cout, Standard Output (STDOUT). The lines of your output may be in a different order, but the output otherwise must match exactly. Here is the expected output for the provided input file puzzle2.txt:<br><figure class="highlight livecodeserver"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="string">'abcd'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="string">'aei'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="string">'bfj'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="string">'cgk'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="string">'dhl'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="string">'efgh'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="string">'ijkl'</span> is <span class="keyword">not</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="built_in">word</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><h3 id="ASCII-Art-Output"><a href="#ASCII-Art-Output" class="headerlink" title="ASCII Art Output"></a>ASCII Art Output</h3><p>If a third argument is specified, you will print an ASCII art representation of the empty puzzle board. The output for the –print option is shown on the right. For full credit, your output must match this sample output exactly.</p><p>The next step is to prepare a template for the list of word clues. When the –print_coordinates option is specified each clue is listed with the position (row and column) of the starting letter of the word and the word direction. This output is shown to the left. Note that the upper left corner of the puzzle grid is position (0,0). It’s ok if your words appear in a different order than this sample output, but the output must otherwise match exactly.</p><p>This output can be used by a crossword puzzle designer, who would take this output and replace the words with clever clues (something probably still best done by humans).</p><h3 id="Submission-Details"><a href="#Submission-Details" class="headerlink" title="Submission Details"></a>Submission Details</h3><p>Do all of your work in a new folder inside of your Data Structures homeworks directory. You should use the C++ STL string and vector classes in your implementation. Use good coding style when you design and implement your program. Review the “Good Programming Practices” section on the course webpage to be sure that the TAs will be able give you credit for your hard work. Organize your program into functions: don’t put all the code in main! Use good variable and function names. Be sure to make up new test cases and don’t forget to comment your code!</p><p>Download and fill out the provided template README.txt file, adding any notes you want the grader to read. You must do this assignment on your own, as described in the “Collaboration Policy &amp; Academic Integrity” handout. If you discuss the problem or error messages, etc. with anyone, please list their names in your README.txt file. Prepare and submit your assignment as instructed on the course webpage. Please ask a TA if you need help preparing your assignment for submission or if you have difficulty writing portable code.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      完成游戏Crossword中的Checker逻辑部分的实现。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
      <category term="Game" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Game/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>COMP1201-Base-Convertor</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMP1201-Base-Convertor.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMP1201-Base-Convertor.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-21T03:30:33.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-21T03:32:11.940Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>A grade school teacher wants to develop a program to generate values to a series of numbers in different base systems. The teacher is limiting the bases to be between 2 and 9, inclusive. Each line of input will have a base value and a sequence of characters representing a nonnegative number in that base. However, each number (sequence of characters) has been placed “backwards”. That is the rightmost digit is first in the sequence, the second digit from the right is encountered next, and so on.</p><p>The program reads the digits one a time. As each digit is read, the program should translate that digit into its corresponding decimal value, and then multiply it by the appropriate power of the base. There is an arbitrary number of blanks between the base and the first digit in the sequence.</p><p>Suppose that the teacher wants the students to convert the binary number 1011.</p><p>The first number, 2, represents the base. Base 2 is designated as binary. The 1101 represents a character sequence of binary digits of the number to convert. IT IS BACKWARDS! This means that the first 1 is in the one’s position or 2 to the 0 power. The second 1 is in the two’s position or 2 to the 1 power. The 0 is in the four’s position or 2 to the second power. And lastly, the rightmost 1 is in the eight’s position or 2 to the third power. Remember the number that was to be converted was 1011.</p><p>The value of this number is 1 1 + 1 2 + 0 4 + 1 8 which equals 11. Please see the sample output on how values are to be displayed.</p><p>Ask your instructor to give another example in a different base.</p><p>However, the teacher’s grade school students have entered the data values. This data CANNOT be trusted as being valid data.</p><p>Your program needs to check for valid bases and if the base is invalid write out a message that says,</p><p>Invalid base given, throwing away the rest of the line.<br>To throw away a line of input use cin.ignore( ). Your instructor will talk about this in class. In addition, your program needs to check for valid digits in the given base. For example, if the base is 2, any digit equal to 2 or higher is NOT legitimate. Your error message should say (i.e. input line is : 2 234510)</p><p>For the given base 2, the number is NOT valid!<br>You will need to throw away the rest of the line here as well.</p><p>Lastly, your program is supposed to add up the values of all valid numbers given and print this value as the final part of the output. If there are NO valid inputted numbers given, then the sum is zero (0).</p><p>Again, please see the sample output on how values are to be displayed.</p><p>The following additional requirements must be followed:</p><h3 id="A"><a href="#A" class="headerlink" title="A"></a>A</h3><p>Your main function should adhere to the following pseudocode:</p><h3 id="B"><a href="#B" class="headerlink" title="B"></a>B</h3><p>The above pseudocode suggests some functions. Keep these functions single-minded, performing a focused task that can be well-named. You should design pseudocode for each of these functions. All function bodies, including the body of main, should be NO more than 30 lines long, including braces, blank lines and comments.</p><h3 id="C"><a href="#C" class="headerlink" title="C"></a>C</h3><p>You must NOT use arrays. You will lose ALL points if you do.</p><h3 id="D"><a href="#D" class="headerlink" title="D"></a>D</h3><p>You must follow the programming standards.</p><h3 id="E"><a href="#E" class="headerlink" title="E"></a>E</h3><p>You must follow the formatting of the sample I/O below.</p><h3 id="F"><a href="#F" class="headerlink" title="F"></a>F</h3><p>You must thoroughly test your program.</p><h3 id="G"><a href="#G" class="headerlink" title="G"></a>G</h3><p>You must use the following functions and you MUST add the documentation for the parameters for functions that have parameters.</p><h3 id="H"><a href="#H" class="headerlink" title="H"></a>H</h3><p>To get credit for the assignment, your solution must minimally work on Test Case # 1 below.</p><p>Sample I/O<br>Below are two sample runs.<br>They do NOT cover all cases.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      完成任意进制数字Base转换器。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS122-Searching</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS122-Searching.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS122-Searching.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-19T07:42:24.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-19T07:43:30.274Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>For this assignment, you will compare the efficiency of searching a sorted linked list and a hash table.</p><p>You should use a variation of your code for Mini-Assignment 3 for this.</p><h3 id="Modifications-from-Mini-Assignment-3"><a href="#Modifications-from-Mini-Assignment-3" class="headerlink" title="Modifications from Mini-Assignment 3"></a>Modifications from Mini-Assignment 3</h3><p>Instead of getting the words to load into the hash table from the user, you must load at least 2000 words from a file called words.txt as input (using file I/O). It is OK if you share the words with classmates for this. Make sure that your words are sorted in random order (more about this later). The words.txt file must be in the same directory as your source code.<br>It’s OK to use more than 2000 words but don’t have more than 10000.<br>The hash table’s buckets must point to sorted linked lists. When you load a word into the hash table, also load the words into one very long sorted linked list. You must call the same function for inserting into the sorted linked list as for inserting into the hash table bucket’s linked list. Do not duplicate code for linked list insertion.<br>Make the hash table 127 buckets in size.<br>You must create a function called searchLinkedList that searches a sorted linked list for a word and returns a pointer to the node containing the word (if found) or NULL.<br>This function must return NULL immediately after you pass the point in the linked list where the word would have been found if it was in the linked list.<br>The function takes three parameters:<br>char <em> searchWord (or you can use a string object): word to search for (entered by the user)<br>struct linkedList </em> linkedList: linked list to search (in your program, you can call the linked list node struct anything that makes sense)<br>int <em> comparisonCount: pointer to int filled in by the function with the count of strcmp comparisons done in searching the linked list<br>Create a search function called searchForWordTwice. It returns nothing and will have the following parameters:<br>char </em> searchWord (or you can use a string object): word to search for (entered by the user)<br>struct linkedList <em> linkedList: linked list to search<br>struct linkedList </em> hashTable[]: hash table to search<br>int comparisonCount[2]: array containing the count of strcmp comparisons done in searching the extremely-long sorted linked list (element 0) and in searching the hash table (element 1)<br>It must call your linked list search function and then displays one of the following messages once the search is done:<br>“word was found in the list in number comparisons”, where word is the word being searched for, list is either “linked list” or “hash table bucket” and number equals the number of times that strcmp was called<br>“word was NOT found in the list in number comparisons”<br>You will use this search function to search the hash table bucket and the sorted linked list.<br>Don’t worry about the grammatical inconsistency of possibly displaying “1 comparisons”.<br>Indent the message displayed by one TAB (‘\t’).<br>Once you are finished the loop, display the total number of searches, the total number of comparisons done by searching the sorted linked list, and the total number of comparisons done by searching the hash table.</p><h3 id="Other-Requirements"><a href="#Other-Requirements" class="headerlink" title="Other Requirements"></a>Other Requirements</h3><p>Design your linked list code so that you do not have to duplicate code unnecessarily. This is very important.<br>Clean up all allocated memory before exiting.<br>Use constants to avoid magic numbers.<br>You can assume that all words will be in lowercase.<br>Your program must compile without warnings. If you have to use a #pragma as stated in the C course notes in order to get rid of the Microsoft-specific warnings, you should do so.<br>Your project must be named dsA2.<br>The source file that contains your main() function must be called dsA2.cpp. Put all hash table-related code in hashing.cpp. Put all linked list-related code in linkedlist.cpp (and linkedlist.h if you are using a class). Create other .h files as needed to support compilation. Do not create any other source files.<br>Remember to put appropriate header comments at the top of ALL source files.<br>Create a JPG file called compare.jpg that contains a screenshot of your program running with a full screen of sample output (so that I can see the difference in comparison count between the methods for at least two successful and three unsuccessful searches (do not skimp on the number of searches)). Make sure that it includes the final summary output. Put this file in the top directory of your project (so that it is submitted with your submission). A sample of this file is provided for you. Please follow the output format and contents exactly. Not providing this file as required could produce an automatically-failing mark in this assignment.<br>Provide your words.txt file in the same directory as your source code.<br>Submit your submission to the appropriate dropbox as required by the SET Submission Standards document.</p><h3 id="Hints"><a href="#Hints" class="headerlink" title="Hints"></a>Hints</h3><p>An easy way to sort the input words in random order is the following:</p><p>Get 2000+ words, one per line. Copy the words to the clipboard.<br>Start Excel.<br>Paste the words into Excel (so that you have one column of 2000+ rows).<br>In the next column, put random numbers using =rand().<br>Select all of the data.<br>Sort the data using the column with the random number as the sorting key.<br>Delete the random number column.<br>Save the data into a text file.<br>Here is a 500 word sample input file.<br>Unit testing your functions is a really good idea. You should not leave your unit testing code in your submitted source.<br>Don’t forget that malloc() does not support C++ string objects so you must use new instead if you have strings as part of a dynamically-allocated struct or class.<br>You can use the examples provided on the DS website and C website as long as you attribute credit in a comment. You must attribute credit for the djb2 hash function (credit the real author Dan Bernstein and state that you got it from lecture).</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      对比分析Sorted linked list和Hash table的搜索效率。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Data Structure" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Data-Structure/"/>
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS208-AVL-Tree</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS208-AVL-Tree.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS208-AVL-Tree.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-16T23:49:30.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-16T23:51:12.826Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>For this project, you will be implementing both a modified AVL tree and a 2-5 tree (this is a 2-4 tree but you are allowed to have up to 5 children as apposed to 4). The code is to be uploaded to gradescope under Programming Assignment 3, where you may test your code against the autograder. Gradescope should be able to run your program using the command “make” followed by “./prog1.out”. Be sure to include all .cpp/.h files that make up your program, the dataset provided a Makefile, and name the executable prog1.out Gradescope has clang++ (clang 10) and a g++ compiler available. Please note that it is possible that your program could have some unexpected behavior on gradescope’s auto grader compared to whatever machine you wrote the code on, so submit your program early and make sure it is bug free on gradescope. You are to implement your own AVL/2-5 trees, so you may not use any libraries that automatically do this for you.</p><h3 id="Implement-AVL-Tree-and-2-5-Tree-classes"><a href="#Implement-AVL-Tree-and-2-5-Tree-classes" class="headerlink" title="Implement AVL Tree and 2-5 Tree classes."></a>Implement AVL Tree and 2-5 Tree classes.</h3><p>Each node in the AVL or 2-5 trees is a pair of (word,counter) where counter shows the number of occurrence of the word in the dataset.</p><p>The AVL trees we will be implementing in this assignment are identical to the AVL trees you learned in class, except that here the height constraint will allow for a height dierence of the subtrees of a given node to be at most 2 (as apposed to 1, which is the version you learned in class. The tree should NOT balance itself if the height dierence is only 2), So your code should only perform rotations if the height dierence is over 2.</p><p>Each class should have at least the following functions:</p><p>A constructor and a destructor.<br>A function for searching a word (the word may or may not exist).<br>A function for inserting a new word or incrementing the counter if the word is already inserted.<br>A function for doing a range search. The function takes as input two words. Given two words, the function should find all the words in between. The resulting words should be sorted.<br>Additionally, in order to verify your data structures, you will need to implement the following methods for both classes:</p><p>A print function that prints out a pre-order traversal of the tree.<br>A function that prints out the height of the tree.</p><p>These last two functions will not be apart of gradescope’s autograder test, but will be used by us to ensure that you have properly implemented the data structures using a modified AVL tree and a 2-5 tree. Please comment your code so it is clear how to use your print and height functions.</p><p>For this project, you should use PA3 dataset.txt available on piazza and gauchospace to initially build your data structures. You are expected to parse the dataset and insert the words contained in it. Insert each word using the insert method you implemented for both trees.</p><p>There should be no output when inserting words from PA3 dataset.txt. For your gradescope submission to be able to access the data set you must upload it and use the path:</p><p>/autograder/submission/PA3 dataset.txt</p><h3 id="Implementation-Details"><a href="#Implementation-Details" class="headerlink" title="Implementation Details"></a>Implementation Details</h3><p>Your code should build a modified AVL tree as described before and a 2-5 tree out of the dataset provided. Gradescope will pass a string of commands via argv1. Each command will be separated by a comma. Your code may receive the following commands: search, insert, range search from [word 1] to [word 2]. Your output should follow this structure EXACTLY to ensure full credit.</p><p>Gradescope will pass a string of commands via argv1. Each command will be separated by a comma. Your code may receive the following commands:</p><p>(a) Search a given word. Both the AVL tree and the 2-5 tree should be searched to find the word. The program should print out “[word] found”, along with the count of the word, once for each data structure. If the word is not found the program should output “[word] not found”, once for each data structure.</p><p>Ex:<br>search hello<br>hello found, count = 2<br>hello found, count = 2</p><p>or if hello is not in the data structure<br>hello not found<br>hello not found<br>(b) Insert a word. If the word is already present then its counter should be increased by one. The program should output “[word] inserted, new count = [count]”, once for each data structure.</p><p>Ex:<br>insert goodbye<br>goodbye inserted, new count = 1<br>goodbye inserted, new count = 1<br>(c) Do a range search. The program should print out all words alphabetically in between (an including) the two words provided in the range search that are in the data structures. Note that the two words given to perform the range search may or may not be in your data structures. The program should do this once for both data structures.</p><p>(d) Print out a traversal of the tree. The program should print out the values of the tree using a pre-order traversal. For each node, you must do the following: print an open parenthesis, the node’s data, print the nodes’ children from left to right, followed by a close-parenthesis.<br>For each datum, you must print the key and value separated by a colon. If a node has multiple data elements, you should delimit them using commas. For any children that are null, you should print empty parentheses.</p><p>(e) Print the height of the tree. The code should simply output: “Height = [height of tree]”</p><h3 id="Full-Test-example"><a href="#Full-Test-example" class="headerlink" title="Full Test example"></a>Full Test example</h3><p>Your program receives the commands through argv1. In the following example we have that that the starting count of hello is 2, of yesterday is 3, and goodbye is not present in the data structure. We also have that the only words in between band and cat in the data structure are band, bankers, bat, and cab. gradescope passes the following commands through argv1:</p><p>search hello, insert goodbye, insert hello, range search band to cat<br>We expect the following output:</p><p>hello found, count = 2<br>hello found, count = 2<br>goodbye inserted, new count = 1<br>goodbye inserted, new count = 1<br>hello inserted, new count = 3<br>hello inserted, new count = 3<br>band<br>bankers<br>bat<br>cab<br>band<br>bankers<br>bat<br>cab</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      实现AVL树，以及改进后的2-5树。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Data Structure" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Data-Structure/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS162-File-IO</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS162-File-IO.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS162-File-IO.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-14T23:43:57.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-14T23:45:19.087Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>In order to get credit for the lab, you need to be checked off by the end of lab. You can earn a maximum of 5 points for lab work completed outside of lab time, but you must finish the lab before the next lab. For extenuating circumstances, contact your lab TAs and the instructor.</p><p>This lab is worth 10 points total. Here’s the breakdown:</p><p>4 point: Design for the problem<br>6 points: Implement your design</p><h3 id="Step-1-Design"><a href="#Step-1-Design" class="headerlink" title="Step 1: Design"></a>Step 1: Design</h3><p>In this lab, you will practice reading and writing to a file, a.k.a. File I/O. You can copy and paste or download this example file.</p><p>The input file provides details for a student database in the following format:<br><figure class="highlight applescript"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">Number_of_students</span><br><span class="line">ID_Number Student_First_Name Student_Last_Name Major</span><br><span class="line">...&lt;Repeats n <span class="built_in">number</span> <span class="keyword">of</span> <span class="keyword">times</span>&gt;...</span><br><span class="line">ID_Number Student_First_Name Student_Last_Name Major</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>Your program will read specific information from the file and continue reading the contents of the body from the file until the EOF (end of file) character. You will write the following information to an output file:</p><p>Sort students by ID number<br>Sort students by last name<br>The number of unique majors</p><p>Each section of information should be labeled in the output file in all capital letters. A struct should be used to store and manipulate the file information between reading and writing the file. You must include the follow three functions with the exact prototypes:</p><p>student <em> create_student_db(int);<br>This function will create the array of student based on the number of students in the file<br>void populate_student_db_info(student </em>, int, ifstream &amp;);<br>This function should do the work of actually reading through the ifstream that represents your opened file and storing the information in a pre-allocated array of student that’s passed in<br>void delete_student_db_info(student **, int);<br>This function will delete all dynamic memory created in your program<br>Your main function needs to check to make sure the file you open exists before moving forward. If the file doesn’t exist, then you need to provide an error message and get a file name that does exist.</p><p>Write a design for the main function in the driver file, driver.cpp.<br>Write a design for the create_student_db(), populate_student_db_info(), and delete_student_db_info() as well as the functions needed to satisfy the above bulleted output functions in the implementation file, student_db.cpp<br>Here’s some documentation that will help you get going with File I/O:</p><p>C++ Basic file I/O: <a href="http://www.learncpp.com/cpp-tutorial/186-basic-file-io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.learncpp.com/cpp-tutorial/186-basic-file-io/</a><br>ifstream: <a href="http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/fstream/ifstream/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/fstream/ifstream/</a><br>ofstream: <a href="http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/fstream/ofstream/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/fstream/ofstream/</a><br>fstream: <a href="http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/fstream/fstream/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/fstream/fstream/</a></p><h3 id="Step-2-Implementation"><a href="#Step-2-Implementation" class="headerlink" title="Step 2: Implementation"></a>Step 2: Implementation</h3><p>Now, implement the driver.cpp, student_db.cpp, and student_db.h files. Create a Makefile to manage the compilation of all these files. You can adapt the Makefile that was posted on the Calendar page in Canvas.</p><p>Remember, you will not receive lab credit if you do not get checked off before leaving each lab. Once you have a zero on a lab, then it cannot be changed because we have no way of knowing if you were there or no t.</p><p>Show your completed work and answers to the TAs for credit. You will not get points if you do not get checked off!</p><p>Submit your work to TEACH for our records (Note: you will not get points if you don’t get checked off with a TA!!!)</p><p>Create a tar archive that contains all files you’ve created in this lab: tar -cvf lab2.tar student_db.h student_db.cpp driver.cpp makefile<br>Transfer the tar file from the ENGR server to your local laptop.<br>Go to TEACH.<br>In the menu on the right side, go to Class Tools Submit Assignment.<br>Select CS162 Lab2 from the list of assignments and click “SUBMIT NOW”<br>Select your files and click the Submit button</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      练习C++中基础I/O处理，读写文件。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CMPT130-Binary-Arithmetic</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CMPT130-Binary-Arithmetic.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CMPT130-Binary-Arithmetic.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-11T01:11:14.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-11T01:12:41.105Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>Read this document in its entirety and carefully before you start anything and understand it. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to email me.</p><p>In this assignment, we will work on arithmetic of integers in two’s complement binary arithmetic. To store the two’s complement representations of integers, we will use the C++ string data type. You are not allowed to use any ARRAY variable in this assignment. Read the restriction section below.<br>Consider the main program given below:<br><figure class="highlight cpp"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br><span class="line">8</span><br><span class="line">9</span><br><span class="line">10</span><br><span class="line">11</span><br><span class="line">12</span><br><span class="line">13</span><br><span class="line">14</span><br><span class="line">15</span><br><span class="line">16</span><br><span class="line">17</span><br><span class="line">18</span><br><span class="line">19</span><br><span class="line">20</span><br><span class="line">21</span><br><span class="line">22</span><br><span class="line">23</span><br><span class="line">24</span><br><span class="line">25</span><br><span class="line">26</span><br><span class="line">27</span><br><span class="line">28</span><br><span class="line">29</span><br><span class="line">30</span><br><span class="line">31</span><br><span class="line">32</span><br><span class="line">33</span><br><span class="line">34</span><br><span class="line">35</span><br><span class="line">36</span><br><span class="line">37</span><br><span class="line">38</span><br><span class="line">39</span><br><span class="line">40</span><br><span class="line">41</span><br><span class="line">42</span><br><span class="line">43</span><br><span class="line">44</span><br><span class="line">45</span><br><span class="line">46</span><br><span class="line">47</span><br><span class="line">48</span><br><span class="line">49</span><br><span class="line">50</span><br><span class="line">51</span><br><span class="line">52</span><br><span class="line">53</span><br><span class="line">54</span><br><span class="line">55</span><br><span class="line">56</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="meta">#<span class="meta-keyword">include</span> <span class="meta-string">&lt;iostream&gt;</span></span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta">#<span class="meta-keyword">include</span> <span class="meta-string">&lt;cmath&gt;</span></span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="meta">#<span class="meta-keyword">include</span> <span class="meta-string">&lt;string&gt;</span></span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="keyword">using</span> <span class="keyword">namespace</span> <span class="built_in">std</span>;</span><br><span class="line"><span class="function"><span class="keyword">int</span> <span class="title">main</span><span class="params">()</span></span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="function"></span>&#123;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Read in the bit pattern size</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">int</span> L;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">do</span></span><br><span class="line">    &#123;</span><br><span class="line">        <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size "</span>;</span><br><span class="line">        <span class="built_in">cin</span> &gt;&gt; L;</span><br><span class="line">    &#125; <span class="keyword">while</span> (L &lt;= <span class="number">0</span>);</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Read in two integers a and b</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">int</span> a, b;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"Enter an integer a "</span>;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cin</span> &gt;&gt; a;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"Enter an integer b "</span>;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cin</span> &gt;&gt; b;</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Calculate the decimal arithmetic sum of a and b and print the result</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">int</span> c1 = a + b;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"In decimal "</span> &lt;&lt; a &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" + "</span> &lt;&lt; b &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is "</span> &lt;&lt; c1 &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Compute the two's complement representations of a and b</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Each integer must be represented in L-bits pattern</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Also these two's complement representations must be returned as string data types</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">string</span> A = decimalToTwocomplementString(a, L);</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">string</span> B = decimalToTwocomplementString(b, L);</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Print the two's complement representations of a and b</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"The two's complement of "</span> &lt;&lt; a &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is\t "</span> &lt;&lt; A &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"The two's complement of "</span> &lt;&lt; b &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is\t "</span> &lt;&lt; B &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Compute the binary sum of the two's complement representations of a and b</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// The result must be returned as L-bit pattern string data type</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">string</span> C = TwoComplementStringAddition(A, B);</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Print the two's complement representation binary sum</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"The binary sum of "</span> &lt;&lt; A &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" and "</span> &lt;&lt; B &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is "</span> &lt;&lt; C &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Convert the two's complement representation binary sum to decimal and print</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">int</span> c2 = TwoComplementStringToDecimal(C);</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"In two's complement arithmetic, "</span> &lt;&lt; a &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" + "</span> &lt;&lt; b &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is "</span> &lt;&lt; c2 &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="comment">// Print some concluding results</span></span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">if</span> (c1 == c2)</span><br><span class="line">        <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; c1 &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is equal to "</span> &lt;&lt; c2 &lt;&lt; <span class="string">". Good Job!"</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">else</span></span><br><span class="line">    &#123;</span><br><span class="line">        <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; c1 &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" is not equal to "</span> &lt;&lt; c2 &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line">        <span class="built_in">cout</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="string">"Either "</span> &lt;&lt; c1 &lt;&lt; <span class="string">" cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!"</span> &lt;&lt; <span class="built_in">endl</span>;</span><br><span class="line">    &#125;</span><br><span class="line">    system(<span class="string">"Pause"</span>);</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="keyword">return</span> <span class="number">0</span>;</span><br><span class="line">&#125;</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><h3 id="Your-Task"><a href="#Your-Task" class="headerlink" title="Your Task"></a>Your Task</h3><p>The main program shown above is uploaded together with this problem statement onto Moodle under Topic 8. Download the main program code and copy and paste it to a new project. You are required to copy the given main program exactly as it is with no change whatsoever. Do not change any function signature. Then implement the missing functions so that the program works correctly. Some sample runs are given below for your reference. Of course, you can write additional helper functions that you can call from within your functions; but you are not allowed to make any change to the given main program.</p><h3 id="Restrictions"><a href="#Restrictions" class="headerlink" title="Restrictions"></a>Restrictions</h3><p>You are required to use C++ string Data Type to represent the two’s complement binary representations. You are not allowed to use any ARRAY variable for any purpose. If you use ARRAY variable for any purpose in your program, you will automatically get zero mark.</p><h3 id="Submission-Format"><a href="#Submission-Format" class="headerlink" title="Submission Format"></a>Submission Format</h3><p>You are required to submit your program online through Moodle. You will find a submission button for Assignment 2 on Moodle under Topic 7 and you are required to upload the source code of your C++ program. No assignment is submitted through email or hard copy; you must upload your work onto Moodle before the due date. Make sure to upload your .cpp file.</p><h3 id="Marking"><a href="#Marking" class="headerlink" title="Marking"></a>Marking</h3><p>A nonworking program will automatically get zero. A program that works but does not give right output or gives partial right output will lose marks depending how severe its shortcoming is.</p><h3 id="Some-sample-runs-of-the-program-are-shown-below"><a href="#Some-sample-runs-of-the-program-are-shown-below" class="headerlink" title="Some sample runs of the program are shown below"></a>Some sample runs of the program are shown below</h3><p>Remark: The user input values and the pressing of the enter key symbol are shown in red color for clarity.</p><p><code>`</code><br>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 5<br>Enter an integer a 9<br>Enter an integer b -14<br>In decimal 9 + -14 is -5<br>The two’s complement of 9 is 01001<br>The two’s complement of -14 is 10010<br>The binary sum of 01001 and 10010 is 11011<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, 9 + -14 is -5</p><h2 id="5-is-equal-to-5-Good-Job"><a href="#5-is-equal-to-5-Good-Job" class="headerlink" title="-5 is equal to -5. Good Job!"></a>-5 is equal to -5. Good Job!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 2<br>Enter an integer a -100<br>Enter an integer b 98<br>In decimal -100 + 98 is -2<br>The two’s complement of -100 is 00<br>The two’s complement of 98 is 10<br>The binary sum of 00 and 10 is 10<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, -100 + 98 is -2</p><h2 id="2-is-equal-to-2-Good-Job"><a href="#2-is-equal-to-2-Good-Job" class="headerlink" title="-2 is equal to -2. Good Job!"></a>-2 is equal to -2. Good Job!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 2<br>Enter an integer a 100<br>Enter an integer b -98<br>In decimal 100 + -98 is 2<br>The two’s complement of 100 is 00<br>The two’s complement of -98 is 10<br>The binary sum of 00 and 10 is 10<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, 100 + -98 is -2<br>2 is not equal to -2</p><h2 id="Either-2-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake"><a href="#Either-2-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake" class="headerlink" title="Either 2 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!"></a>Either 2 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 8<br>Enter an integer a 62<br>Enter an integer b -99<br>In decimal 62 + -99 is -37<br>The two’s complement of 62 is 00111110<br>The two’s complement of -99 is 10011101<br>The binary sum of 00111110 and 10011101 is 11011011<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, 62 + -99 is -37</p><h2 id="37-is-equal-to-37-Good-Job"><a href="#37-is-equal-to-37-Good-Job" class="headerlink" title="-37 is equal to -37. Good Job!"></a>-37 is equal to -37. Good Job!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 5<br>Enter an integer a 11<br>Enter an integer b 9<br>In decimal 11 + 9 is 20<br>The two’s complement of 11 is 01011<br>The two’s complement of 9 is 01001<br>The binary sum of 01011 and 01001 is 10100<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, 11 + 9 is -12<br>20 is not equal to -12</p><h2 id="Either-20-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake"><a href="#Either-20-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake" class="headerlink" title="Either 20 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!"></a>Either 20 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 5<br>Enter an integer a -321<br>Enter an integer b 305<br>In decimal -321 + 305 is -16<br>The two’s complement of -321 is 11111<br>The two’s complement of 305 is 10001<br>The binary sum of 11111 and 10001 is 10000<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, -321 + 305 is -16</p><h2 id="16-is-equal-to-16-Good-Job"><a href="#16-is-equal-to-16-Good-Job" class="headerlink" title="-16 is equal to -16. Good Job!"></a>-16 is equal to -16. Good Job!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 3<br>Enter an integer a 2<br>Enter an integer b 2<br>In decimal 2 + 2 is 4<br>The two’s complement of 2 is 010<br>The two’s complement of 2 is 010<br>The binary sum of 010 and 010 is 100<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, 2 + 2 is -4<br>4 is not equal to -4</p><h2 id="Either-4-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake"><a href="#Either-4-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake" class="headerlink" title="Either 4 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!"></a>Either 4 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 6<br>Enter an integer a 45<br>Enter an integer b -17<br>In decimal 45 + -17 is 28<br>The two’s complement of 45 is 101101<br>The two’s complement of -17 is 101111<br>The binary sum of 101101 and 101111 is 011100<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, 45 + -17 is 28</p><h2 id="28-is-equal-to-28-Good-Job"><a href="#28-is-equal-to-28-Good-Job" class="headerlink" title="28 is equal to 28. Good Job!"></a>28 is equal to 28. Good Job!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 1<br>Enter an integer a -99<br>Enter an integer b 100<br>In decimal -99 + 100 is 1<br>The two’s complement of -99 is 1<br>The two’s complement of 100 is 0<br>The binary sum of 1 and 0 is 1<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, -99 + 100 is -1<br>1 is not equal to -1</p><h2 id="Either-1-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake"><a href="#Either-1-cannot-be-represented-by-the-given-bit-pattern-OR-we-have-made-some-mistake" class="headerlink" title="Either 1 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!"></a>Either 1 cannot be represented by the given bit pattern OR we have made some mistake!</h2><p>Enter positive integer for the bit pattern size 1<br>Enter an integer a -100<br>Enter an integer b 99<br>In decimal -100 + 99 is -1<br>The two’s complement of -100 is 0<br>The two’s complement of 99 is 1<br>The binary sum of 0 and 1 is 1<br>In two’s complement arithmetic, -100 + 99 is -1<br>-1 is equal to -1. Good Job!<br><code></code></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      使用C++对Binary Number进行算术运算。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Web" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Web/"/>
    
      <category term="Database" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Database/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CMSC132-Tetris-Game</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CMSC132-Tetris-Game.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CMSC132-Tetris-Game.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-09T02:13:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-09T02:15:51.795Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Overview"><a href="#Overview" class="headerlink" title="Overview"></a>Overview</h3><p>For this project, you will implement code for the Tetris game. The graphical user interface has been provided to you in a package called gui. No part of the assignment involves you making any changes to code in this package. You will be implementing some of the functionality for the Tetris game by modifying classes provided to you in the model package.</p><h3 id="Objectives"><a href="#Objectives" class="headerlink" title="Objectives"></a>Objectives</h3><p>This project will allow you to practice two-dimensional arrays, abstract classes, inheritance, and test development.</p><h3 id="Grading"><a href="#Grading" class="headerlink" title="Grading"></a>Grading</h3><p>Public Tests (50%)<br>Release Tests (40%)<br>Style (10%)</p><h3 id="Code-Distribution"><a href="#Code-Distribution" class="headerlink" title="Code Distribution"></a>Code Distribution</h3><p>You are provided with the following packages:</p><p>gui - Represents the graphical user interface for the game. Executing the main method of the GameGUI class in this package will launch the user interface (assuming your code compiles successfully).<br>model - Includes the classes you need to implement.<br>tests - Includes the public tests. You should add your student test class to this package.</p><h3 id="Layout-and-Rotation"><a href="#Layout-and-Rotation" class="headerlink" title="Layout and Rotation"></a>Layout and Rotation</h3><p>The layout of a tetromino represents its shape. When a tetromino rotates, its layout changes. Each tetromino has 4 layouts: up, left, down and right. When originally created, a tetromino is in the up layout. After one left rotation, it shifts to the left layout. After a second left rotation, it shifts to the down layout. After a third left rotation, it shifts to the right layout. Finally, after a fourth left rotation, it returns to a up layout. This sequence can be repeated by pressing z during game play. After going from the up layout to the up layout again, i.e in one full rotation through each 90 degree phase, all tetromino’s except from the I tetromino should occupy the same column coordinate as they did initially (If they have been moved down in during the rotation, their row coordinate may have changed). The I tetromino, however, should move left by one position after one complete counter-clockwise rotation. Therefore, the “rotation” of a I tetromino is really a translation, with each full rotation moving it one column closer to the left of the game board.</p><p>The diagram below shows the progression of each tetromino as you rotate counter-clockwise by 90 degrees.</p><h3 id="Location"><a href="#Location" class="headerlink" title="Location"></a>Location</h3><p>Although the layout of a tetromino is set (because its shape is set) for each of the 4 possible orientations, the location of a layed out tetromino will change due to rotation and moving the tetromino left/right. The diagram below illustrates this for the I tetromino.</p><h3 id="Game-Play"><a href="#Game-Play" class="headerlink" title="Game Play"></a>Game Play</h3><p>A random sequence of Tetrominos will fall down the playing field from the centre. The goal of the game is to fill the gaps horizontally. When an entire row is filled, the rows above it will collapse down by one row. A player can move a tetromino left/right using the corresponding arrow keys. They can also rotate the tetromino left (counter-clockwise) 90 degrees at a time by pressing the z key.</p><h3 id="Specification"><a href="#Specification" class="headerlink" title="Specification"></a>Specification</h3><p>You are expected to implement methods for the Tetromino, I, J, L, O, S, T and Z classes. The other classes have been provided and you should not modify them. You should familiarize yourself with the Tetris Class.</p><h3 id="Requirements-Project-Policies"><a href="#Requirements-Project-Policies" class="headerlink" title="Requirements/Project Policies"></a>Requirements/Project Policies</h3><p>You may not add any classes, but feel free to add any instance variables and private methods you understand are necessary.<br>See Style Guidelines for information regarding style.<br>We cannot provide any information regarding release and secret tests. Once your project has been graded, you can see a TA if you would like to find out why you failed a release or secret test.</p><h3 id="Testing"><a href="#Testing" class="headerlink" title="Testing"></a>Testing</h3><p>We encourage you to run the game GUI and interact with the game. However, such an interaction is not guaranteed to test the full range of your code. As such, we also encourage you to write student tests. Student tests demonstrating a particular issue you are encountering with your code will be requested upon seeking help during office hours.</p><h3 id="Submission"><a href="#Submission" class="headerlink" title="Submission"></a>Submission</h3><p>To submit your project, zip the project folder and upload the zipped file to gradescope.</p><h3 id="Tips-on-Getting-Started"><a href="#Tips-on-Getting-Started" class="headerlink" title="Tips on Getting Started"></a>Tips on Getting Started</h3><p>You have been provided with a class to represent each possible Tetris piece (a tetromino). We suggest that you start with the simplest tetromino (like O or I).</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      实现游戏Tetris，也就是俄罗斯方块，GUI部分已经提供，只需要编写逻辑部分即可。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Java" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/Java/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Web" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Web/"/>
    
      <category term="Database" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Database/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ICS46-Final-Project</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/ICS46-Final-Project.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/ICS46-Final-Project.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-06T01:24:48.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-06T01:27:43.338Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Some-ground-rules-READ-THESE-FIRST"><a href="#Some-ground-rules-READ-THESE-FIRST" class="headerlink" title="Some ground rules READ THESE FIRST"></a>Some ground rules READ THESE FIRST</h3><p>This final project asks you to work on a number of separate problems. You’ll begin with a project template in the ICS 46 VM, as you would in any other project, and will need to submit files that meet certain naming and format requirements, similar to the Reinforcement Exercises; as with those exercises, you’ll submit as PDF files (which must be typed, rather than scans of written text). You must follow specifically these requirements or we will not be grading your work.</p><p>You are required to work on these tasks entirely individually. Piazza has been deactivated for question-asking for precisely this reason, though the course staff will still field questions via email, as usual, though we can only help you to understand what a question is asking; we won’t be willing or able to help you figure out how to answer it.</p><p>The late policy does not apply to this project. It is due on Monday, June 8, 11:59pm, after which (beyond the usual ten-minute grace period) no submissions will be accepted and the submission area on Checkmate will disappear.</p><p>We’ll be grading these on the basis of correctness, as well as whether you stay on topic. For problems where you’re asked to explain an answer, we reserve the right to deduct for large amounts of irrelevant information in which a relevant answer is buried; stick with what needs to be said to make your point, rather than just dumping everything you know in hopes that some of it is correct. Also, unlike the Reinforcement Exercises, there will be no points for honest attempts that are incorrect.</p><h3 id="Getting-started"><a href="#Getting-started" class="headerlink" title="Getting started"></a>Getting started</h3><p>Before you begin work on these problems, there’s a chore that you’ll need to complete on your ICS 46 VM to get it set up to proceed.</p><h3 id="Refreshing-your-ICS-46-VM-environment"><a href="#Refreshing-your-ICS-46-VM-environment" class="headerlink" title="Refreshing your ICS 46 VM environment"></a>Refreshing your ICS 46 VM environment</h3><p>Even if you previously downloaded your ICS 46 VM, you may need to refresh its environment before proceeding with this project, so that you have a copy of the final project template that you’ll need for this project.</p><p>Log into your VM and issue the command ics46 version to see what version of the ICS 46 environment you currently have stored on your VM. Note, in particular, the timestamp; if you see a version with a timestamp older than the one listed below, you’ll want to refresh your environment by running the command ics46 refresh to download the latest one before you proceed with this project.</p><p>Note that you can instead use the ics46 refresh_local technique described in the Project #1 write-up, if you’re unable to make your outgoing Internet connection work from within the ICS 46 VM.</p><h3 id="Creating-your-project-directory-on-your-ICS-46-VM"><a href="#Creating-your-project-directory-on-your-ICS-46-VM" class="headerlink" title="Creating your project directory on your ICS 46 VM"></a>Creating your project directory on your ICS 46 VM</h3><p>A project template has been created specifically for this project. It includes a gather script for preparing your files for submission when you’re finished, as well as the usual array of scripts for running the program with and without the Memcheck tool, and a directory in which you can (optionally) write unit tests to assist in your testing.</p><p>Decide on a name for your project directory, then issue the command ics46 start PROJECT_NAME final to create your new project using the final template.</p><p>Do not use other project templates, like basic or project4, for this project!</p><p>Problem 1<br>Suppose that you’ve decided to write this function, which takes an unsigned int parameter and generates a std::string containing that number of randomly-chosen uppercase letters.<br><figure class="highlight arduino"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br><span class="line">8</span><br><span class="line">9</span><br><span class="line">10</span><br><span class="line">11</span><br><span class="line">12</span><br><span class="line">13</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="function"><span class="built_in">std</span>::<span class="built_in">string</span> <span class="title">generateRandomLetters</span><span class="params">(<span class="keyword">unsigned</span> <span class="keyword">int</span> <span class="built_in">size</span>)</span></span></span><br><span class="line"><span class="function"></span>&#123;</span><br><span class="line">  <span class="function"><span class="built_in">std</span>::<span class="built_in">string</span> <span class="title">s</span><span class="params">(<span class="built_in">size</span>, <span class="string">' '</span>)</span></span>;</span><br><span class="line">  <span class="keyword">for</span> (<span class="keyword">unsigned</span> <span class="keyword">int</span> i = <span class="number">0</span>; i [ <span class="built_in">size</span>; ++i)</span><br><span class="line">  &#123;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">std</span>::random_device device;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">std</span>::default_random_engine engine&#123;device()&#125;;</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">std</span>::uniform_int_distribution distribution&#123;<span class="string">'A'</span>, <span class="string">'Z'</span>&#125;;</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">    s[i] = distribution(engine);</span><br><span class="line">  &#125;</span><br><span class="line">  <span class="keyword">return</span> s;</span><br><span class="line">&#125;</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><ol><li>Are there any circumstances in which you wouldn’t expect this function to do what’s specified (i.e., to generate a string of random uppercase letters)? Briefly explain why or why not.</li><li>What adjustments, if any, would you make to the design of this function to improve it? You don’t need to rewrite the function, as long as you explain briefly what you would change about it and why.</li></ol><h3 id="Problem-2"><a href="#Problem-2" class="headerlink" title="Problem 2"></a>Problem 2</h3><p>Suppose that you wrote a C++ class template that implemented singly-linked list with head and tail pointers, and that you used std::shared_ptrs to link the nodes (i.e., the head pointer in the list would be a std::shared_ptr to the first node, the last pointer in the list would be a std::shared_ptr to the last node, and each node would contain a std::shared_ptr to the subsequent node).</p><p>It would seem undoubtedly true that the use of smart pointers would result in you having to write less code, given that smart pointers automate some things that you might otherwise have to write yourself. Suppose, for example, that you implemented the destructor and realized that you could use the ownership characteristics of smart pointers to write this.</p><p>Assuming that all class invariants were intact before calling this destructor (i.e., the pointers are pointing to reasonable places beforehand), are there any circumstances in which you wouldn’t expect all of the nodes to be destroyed properly? If so, briefly explain each circumstance where it would fail to destroy all of the nodes. If not, briefly explain what happens after setting head to nullptr to cause all of the nodes to be destroyed.</p><h3 id="Problem-3"><a href="#Problem-3" class="headerlink" title="Problem 3"></a>Problem 3</h3><p>Suppose you started with an empty AVL tree, then added a sequence of n ascending, consecutive keys to it, starting with 1, then 2, then 3, and so on, until you had added all n of them. (How do you know what n is? See below.)</p><p>List your n value, then list all of the rotations that occurred, one per line, in the order that they occurred. Each rotation should be written using its name and the key in the node where the rotation is rooted (just before the rotation is done) listed in parentheses. For example, if your n value was 27 and you thought that there were three rotations, an LL rotation rooted at 4, an RR rotation rooted at 1, and an LR rotation rooted at 19, you would write this.</p><h3 id="Problem-4"><a href="#Problem-4" class="headerlink" title="Problem 4"></a>Problem 4</h3><p>Let’s imagine that you’re storing information about the current location of a large number of objects in discrete three-dimensional space, which is to say that each location is made up of three unsigned integers x, y, and z, indicating a distance east, a distance north, and a height from some origin point. You can assume that the distances are measured in small amounts, such as millimeters, so that the numbers themselves might be quite large and that they might be distributed quite sparsely. It’s not particularly important what the application is, but let’s imagine that the most common operations are to add a new location to the set and to check whether a location is already in the set.</p><p>You’ve decided that a hash table would be an appropriate way to solve this problem, because you know that a well-chosen hash function can lead to something akin to (1) lookups and amortized (1) insertions, which sounds pretty good to you. Let’s suppose that you’ve chosen this hash function: x + y + z.</p><p>Is x + y + z a good hash function? If so, briefly explain why it’s sufficient; if not, briefly explain what’s wrong with it, though you need not propose a new hash function to replace it.</p><h3 id="Problem-5"><a href="#Problem-5" class="headerlink" title="Problem 5"></a>Problem 5</h3><p>Let’s assume that a bipartite graph is an undirected graph in which there are two distinct sets of vertices, such that all of the edges in the graph connect a vertex in one set to a vertex in the other, but no edges connect vertices in the same set. That sounds esoteric, but there are plenty of real-world problems that collapse nicely into a graph that has these characteristics.</p><p>Now let’s assume that you’d like to implement a bipartite graph, so you consider using either an adjacency matrix or adjacency lists, but wonder if they can be modified if you know ahead of time that the graph will be bipartite.</p><h3 id="Problem-6"><a href="#Problem-6" class="headerlink" title="Problem 6"></a>Problem 6</h3><p>We say that a circle is a directed graph in which the vertices could be given a numbering from 1 through n (i.e., each vertex could be given a unique number), where vertex 1 has one outgoing edge leading to vertex 2, vertex 2 has one outgoing edge leading to vertex 3, and so on. Vertex n has one outgoing edge leading back to vertex 1.</p><h3 id="Problem-7"><a href="#Problem-7" class="headerlink" title="Problem 7"></a>Problem 7</h3><p>In this course, we saw no fewer than nine different ways to sort a sequence of values, but computer science has much to say about this topic, so there’s plenty more to it than we’ve had a chance to discuss.</p><p>For example, we saw that we could use randomness to our advantage in a few places in this course. Skip lists decide randomly on a number of copies of each node, yet leads to logarithmic time lookups, insertions, and removals. Quicksort performs admirably when pivots are chosen randomly. So it’s certainly true that injecting randomness into an algorithm can be a benefit. But let’s take that idea to its logical conclusion. Can you solve problems completely at random?<br>One way we could apply that idea is to the problem of sorting. One way to sort values might be as simple as this.</p><h3 id="Deliverables"><a href="#Deliverables" class="headerlink" title="Deliverables"></a>Deliverables</h3><p>After using the gather script in your project directory to gather up the .cpp, .hpp, and/or .pdf files from your problems directory into a single final.tar.gz file, then submit that file (and only that file!) to Checkmate. Be sure, too, that it contains properly-named files (and files in the proper format) so that they will be graded; we’re not asking for a lot, just some attention to detail.</p><p>Follow this link for a discussion of how to submit your project via Checkmate. Be aware that I’ll be holding you to all of the rules specified in that document, including the one that says that you’re responsible for submitting the version of the project that you want graded. We won’t regrade your work simply because you submitted the wrong version accidentally. (It’s not a bad idea to look at the contents of your tarball on your host operating system before submitting it.)</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      使VM环境，完成7个C++编程问题。包括shared_ptr, linked list, AVL tree, graph, sort等问题。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Web" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Web/"/>
    
      <category term="Database" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Database/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>FIT9131-Koala-Rescue</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/FIT9131-Koala-Rescue.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/FIT9131-Koala-Rescue.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-05T02:19:39.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-05T02:21:34.921Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h3><p>Please note the section on plagiarism in this document.</p><p>In preparing your assignment please note the following:</p><p>The assignment must be done using the BlueJ environment.<br>The Java source code for the assignment must be implemented according to the FIT9131 Java Coding Standards.<br>You must acknowledge all code in your assignment that you have taken from other sources.<br>Only a text interface is to be used for this program, there is to be no GUI. More marks will be gained for a game that is easy to follow with clear information/error messages.<br>Any points needing clarification may be discussed with your tutor in the lab classes. You should not make any assumptions about the program without consulting your tutor.</p><p>Completion of this assignment contributes towards the following FIT9131 learning outcomes:</p><p>design, construct, test and document small computer programs using Java;<br>interpret and demonstrate software engineering principles of maintainability, readability, and modularisation;<br>explain and apply the concepts of the “object-oriented” style of programming.</p><h3 id="Specification"><a href="#Specification" class="headerlink" title="Specification"></a>Specification</h3><p>For this assignment you will simulate the work of a koala rescue team. This section specifies the required functionality of the program.</p><h3 id="Background"><a href="#Background" class="headerlink" title="Background"></a>Background</h3><p>The koala is a marsupial and is native to Australia. Koalas typically live in open eucalyptus (gum tree) forests. Koalas live mainly in trees and eat up to 1 kg of leaves per day. Their diet is restricted to a few varieties of gum trees (e.g., Manna Gum, Swamp Gum, Blue Gum, and River Red Gum). Koalas use some other varieties of trees (e.g. Wattle) for shelter on hot days. Only one koala at a time will occupy a shelter tree. Whilst moving on the ground between trees, koalas are exposed to attacks from predators.</p><p>After bushfires in January 2020, several koala reserves were left devastated when forest habitat burnt leaving many koalas dead or injured and without sufficient food. The koala rescue team’s work is to inspect the reserves and provide help to the koalas. Unfortunately, the team operates within a restricted budget and sometimes has to make difficult decisions. The aim of the rescue team is to save as many koalas as possible within a limited budget.</p><p>The koala reserve consists of a series of observation points where the rescue team pauses, observes the koala population, the trees, and the predators, and decides how the koalas can be helped. The help may be to move a koala to a safe haven if it is injured or there is not enough food or shelter.</p><h3 id="Koala-Rescue-Team-simulation"><a href="#Koala-Rescue-Team-simulation" class="headerlink" title="Koala Rescue Team simulation"></a>Koala Rescue Team simulation</h3><p>The Koala Rescue Team simulation begins with a welcome message and an invitation to the rescue team leader to enter his/her name. The name cannot be blank but must be less than 16 alphabetic characters. The leader is then asked to enter the budget for the rescue. This is an amount from $100 to $200, inclusive.</p><p>The program then sets up the numbers of trees, koalas and predators in each of the 10 observation points as follows:</p><p>The numbers of trees in the reserve are read from a text file trees.txt. The numbers of each type of tree (Manna Gum, Swamp Gum, Blue Gum, River Red Gum, Wattle) at each observation point are read in from the file. The file has 10 lines, with 5 comma separated numbers on each line. Each line represents the tree numbers at each observation point. There is no other reading from the file during the actual running of the program.</p><p>Each tree is either used for shelter or food. Each shelter tree can hold a maximum of one koala. The food trees can produce a certain weight of leaves per day that can be eaten by the koalas (see Table 1 ). The weight is used to calculate the total food available for the koalas at any observation point. The food available is calculated by multiplying the number of each tree type by the weight of leaves it produces and summing these to get the total food available. Each koala, whether healthy or injured, can eat 1 kg of leaves per day.</p><p>Each koala will have a randomly allocated age of 1-18 years.</p><p>There is a random number of 0-4 predators at each observation point.</p><p>There are no koalas in safe haven at the start of the rescue.</p><p>The rescue team visits each of 10 observation points in turn. At each observation point the rescue team considers the number of trees, the number and condition of the koalas (some of which may be injured) and the number of predators. The team takes actions to help the koalas at each point. If the budget runs out at any point then the rescue mission continues but no actions can be taken that involve cost. The rescue mission is considered successful when all areas have been observed and all koalas have survived.</p><h3 id="Class-Design"><a href="#Class-Design" class="headerlink" title="Class Design"></a>Class Design</h3><p>Your program must consist of at least seven classes. A suggested class design is shown in</p><h4 id="Important-Notes"><a href="#Important-Notes" class="headerlink" title="Important Notes"></a>Important Notes</h4><p>Your program must demonstrate your understanding of the object-oriented concepts and general programming constructs presented in FIT9131. Consider carefully your choice of classes, how they interact and the fields and methods of each class. You must use appropriate data structures to store the various objects (observation points, koalas, trees, etc.) in the program. You must make use of both Arrays and ArrayLists in your program. Make sure that you discuss your design with your tutor. You must document any additional assumptions you made.<br>You will be required to justify your design and the choice of any data structures used at the interview.<br>Validation of values for fields and local variables should be implemented where appropriate. You should not allow an object of a class to be set to an invalid state (i.e. put some simple validations in your mutator methods).<br>Your program should handle incorrect or invalid input and present the user with relevant error messages. No invalid input should crash the program.<br>Exception handling should be used where appropriate.</p><h3 id="Interview"><a href="#Interview" class="headerlink" title="Interview"></a>Interview</h3><p>You will be asked to demonstrate your program at an “interview” following the submission date.</p><p>At the interview, you will be asked to explain your code/design, modify your code, and discuss your design decisions and alternatives. Marks will not be awarded for any section of code/design/functionality that you cannot explain satisfactorily (the marker may also delete excessive in-code comments before you are asked to explain that code).</p><p>In other words, you will be assessed on your understanding of the code, and not on the actual code itself.</p><p>The interviews will be organised during week 12 and will take place online via Zoom or other video facility after that time. You must have audio and video available and operating during the interview. It is your responsibility to make yourself available for an interview time and ensure that you have the audio and video capabilities. Any student who does not attend an interview will receive a mark of 0 for the assignment.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      实现一个考拉(Koala)救援小组模拟器。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="JAVA" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/JAVA/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Web" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Web/"/>
    
      <category term="Database" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Database/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS207-Ticket-Vendor</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS207-Ticket-Vendor.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS207-Ticket-Vendor.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-04T01:28:44.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-04T01:30:35.243Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Specification"><a href="#Specification" class="headerlink" title="Specification"></a>Specification</h3><p>Create a program that keeps track of ticket sales for an auditorium that has 32 rows of seats with a varied number of seats in each row. Each ticket is associated with a seat (row letter and seat number such as A12), a price (low $10, medium $30, or high $50), whether or not the seat is for sale or complementary (for example, sold to the public or given to friends of a performer), name of occupant (who bought the ticket), their e-mail address, and the date, time, and name of the performance so that tickets for each seat can be sold to different people at different times.</p><p>It should be possible to get a list of names of all people who bought tickets for a particular date. For a given performance, it should also be possible to print a grid of x’s and o’s where an x represents a seat that is occupied (that is, it’s associated ticket has been sold) and an o represents seats for which no ticket has yet been sold.</p><p>Anyone who buys a high-priced ticket automatically joins the Gold Members Club which is an e-mail list. It should be possible to generate an e-mail list of all people in the Gold Members Club, and to delete someone from that e-mail list upon request.</p><p>A ticket holder should be able to create and access an account that stores the seats, dates, and names of performances attached to all of the tickets which they have purchased.</p><h3 id="Classes"><a href="#Classes" class="headerlink" title="Classes"></a>Classes</h3><p>This is where major design decisions are made. Can we store all of the information in the UserAccounts?</p><p>No, because we do not want to accidentally sell the same seat to the same show to two different people. So information about each show should be stored separately from the user accounts.</p><p>Could we have a ShowManager which keeps instances of class Show in which we store in- formation associated with each seat and ticket?</p><p>Alternatively, could we let seats be entries in a collection or multi-dimensional array that exists within the Show class, generating tickets for each by accessing a TicketManager?</p><p>There are many good designs that can fulfill this specification. When creating CRC cards, you need to choose one design, work with it, and adjust it as problems arise.</p><h3 id="Responsibilities"><a href="#Responsibilities" class="headerlink" title="Responsibilities"></a>Responsibilities</h3><p>More than one class needs access to the seat number and row number of a given ticket. Where should we store that information?</p><p>For the purposes of this handout, we decide to have a Ticket class. But where do we instantiate Ticket? In the TicketManager and pass it to the UserAccount, or should we instantiate the ticket class in the UserAccount and pass that information to the Show and its associated TicketManager?</p><p>Likewise, should we store the e-mail list in the TicketVendorSystem, or create a method that generates that list whenever we need it? If the latter, how do we store the information about whether or not a user is on that list?</p><h3 id="Collaborations"><a href="#Collaborations" class="headerlink" title="Collaborations"></a>Collaborations</h3><p>Collaborators can be classes that are adjacent on the inheritance hierarchy (that is, one is the parent of the other), or instantiate one inside the other, or one gets passed as an argument into a method in the other.</p><p>Collaboration is symmetric. So, if class A collaborates with class B, then class B collaborates with class A. For example, the TicketManager will collaborate with Ticket objects (through instantiation), so the TicketManager collaborates with class Ticket (through creating and storing instances of Ticket).</p><p>On the next page is one possible set of CRC cards that describes one piece of software that fulfills the given specification. Class names are at the top of each card. The responsibilities (variables and methods) of that class are written on the left, while collaborating classes are listed on the right.</p><h3 id="Warm-Up-Questions"><a href="#Warm-Up-Questions" class="headerlink" title="Warm-Up Questions"></a>Warm-Up Questions</h3><p>According to the CRC cards, where is the user’s name stored?<br>How does the system generate a list of users names for a given show?<br>How does the system generate the map of seats with x’s and o’s showing which seats are available? Can you think of another way to accomplish this?</p><h3 id="Questions-About-The-Current-Design"><a href="#Questions-About-The-Current-Design" class="headerlink" title="Questions About The Current Design"></a>Questions About The Current Design</h3><p>In which class does execution start?<br>Where does class Show get instantiated?<br>Where are instances of class Ticket stored?<br>How does a UserAccount get information about available seats for a particular show?<br>How does a user buy a ticket (represented by a Ticket)?<br>Once a Ticket is generated, where does it go? How many classes have direct or in- direct access to the information contained in that Ticket?<br>Should UserAccount collaborate with class Show? Why or why not?</p><h3 id="Questions-About-Changing-the-Design"><a href="#Questions-About-Changing-the-Design" class="headerlink" title="Questions About Changing the Design:"></a>Questions About Changing the Design:</h3><p>Do we need a separate class for Show or can we reorganize the ShowManager so we no longer need instances of Show? If so, should we?<br>How can we change the design so that the same TicketVendorSystem sells tickets to multiple venues (different rooms with different numbers of rows and columns of seats)?</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      使用CRC的方式，设计一款售票系统。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="PHP" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/PHP/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Web" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Web/"/>
    
      <category term="Database" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Database/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>COMP3005-Online-Bookstore</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMP3005-Online-Bookstore.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMP3005-Online-Bookstore.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-03T08:04:13.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-03T08:05:51.152Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Problem-Statement"><a href="#Problem-Statement" class="headerlink" title="Problem Statement"></a>Problem Statement</h3><p>Design and implement an application for an online bookstore (Look Inna Book). This application lets users browse a collection of books that are available in the bookstore. A user can search the bookstore by book name, author name, ISBN, genre, etc.. When a book is selected, information on the author(s), genre, publisher, number of pages, price, etc. can be viewed. A user can select as many books as she likes to be added to the checkout basket. A user needs to be registered in the bookstore to be able to checkout. When checking out, the user inserts billing and shipping information (can be different than those used in registration), and completes the order. The bookstore has the feature of tracking an order via an order number. A user can use this order number to track where the order is currently. Although shipping is carried out by a third-party shipping service, the online bookstore should have the tracking information available for when the user inquires about an order using the order number. Assume all books are shipped from only one warehouse (no multiple order numbers for multiple books shipped from multiple warehouses). The bookstore owners can add new books to their collections, or remove books from their store. They also need to store information on the publishers of books such as name, address, email address, phone number(s), banking account. The banking account for publishers is used to transfer a percentage of the sales of books published by these publishers. This percentage is variable and changes from one book to another. The owners should have access to reports that show sales vs. expenditures, sales per genres, sales per author, etc.. The application should also be able to automatically place orders for new books if the remaining quantity is less than a given threshold (e.g., 10 books). This is done by sending an email to the publisher of the limited books to order a number of books equal to how many books were sold in the previous month (you do not have to implement the email sending component).</p><h3 id="Project-Report"><a href="#Project-Report" class="headerlink" title="Project Report"></a>Project Report</h3><p>You need to submit one report file that contains the following sections. You can add other sections, but the following sections (except Bonus Features) must be in the report:</p><h3 id="Conceptual-Design"><a href="#Conceptual-Design" class="headerlink" title="Conceptual Design"></a>Conceptual Design</h3><p>This section should explain the conceptual design of the database. That is, the ER-diagram of the database for the bookstore and explanation of all the assumptions made in the diagram regarding cardinalities and participation types. Make sure that the assumptions do not contradict with the problem statement in Section 1.</p><h3 id="Reduction-to-Relation-Schemas"><a href="#Reduction-to-Relation-Schemas" class="headerlink" title="Reduction to Relation Schemas"></a>Reduction to Relation Schemas</h3><p>Reduce your ER-diagram into relation schemas and list these in this section.</p><h3 id="Normalization-of-Relation-Schemas"><a href="#Normalization-of-Relation-Schemas" class="headerlink" title="Normalization of Relation Schemas"></a>Normalization of Relation Schemas</h3><p>This section should show that your relation schemas are either in a good normal form (show tests), or if they are not, show how to decompose them into a good normal form (show decomposition work), then show the testing work to make sure that they are in a good normal form.</p><h3 id="Database-Schema-Diagram"><a href="#Database-Schema-Diagram" class="headerlink" title="Database Schema Diagram"></a>Database Schema Diagram</h3><p>This section should show the final schema diagram for the database of the bookstore. This diagram should be similar to the schema diagram of the university database that we study in this course.</p><h3 id="Implementation"><a href="#Implementation" class="headerlink" title="Implementation"></a>Implementation</h3><p>Feel free to use whichever programming language(s) for your application. Your application can be a web-based application, or a desktop application. In this section, you should describe the architecture of your application. That is, what the modules in your application are and how they interact. You are encouraged to include a diagram of the application’s architecture and explain (in text) scenarios of using the application and the workflow of your application.</p><p>Your application should have two different user interfaces: The first is for the users of the application through which the user can browse and buy books. The second is for the bookstore owners/managers through which they can add/remove books, display reports, etc. (more details about the application’s features can be found in Section 1).</p><p>Include screenshots of your application’s two interfaces in different scenarios (e.g., checking out, displaying a report, etc.).</p><h3 id="Bonus-Features-Optional-Section"><a href="#Bonus-Features-Optional-Section" class="headerlink" title="Bonus Features (Optional Section)"></a>Bonus Features (Optional Section)</h3><p>You are free to add bonus features to your online bookstore. You will be rewarded bonus marks for these features. The choice of bonus features is entirely up to you. An example of a bonus feature is approximate search for books. For example, when the user searches for “The Lord of The Rings”, the user would find multiple matches “The Lord of The Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring”, “The Lord of The Rings: The Two Towers”, “The Lord of The Rings: The Return of the King”, “Lord of Flies”, etc., assuming that these were the titles of the books in the database. Note that this approximate match is not limited to matching prefixes only. Another example of a bonus feature would be to show similar books (e.g., other books by the same author, or other books with the same genre). The latter feature is a good example of using views.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      设计并实现一个Online bookstore应用，网站或桌面应用皆可，需要包含数据库设计。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="PHP" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/PHP/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Web" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Web/"/>
    
      <category term="Database" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Database/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>COMPS311-Android-App</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMPS311-Android-App.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/COMPS311-Android-App.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-02T03:09:53.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-02T03:11:48.023Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Question-1-Basics-and-resources"><a href="#Question-1-Basics-and-resources" class="headerlink" title="Question 1 - Basics and resources"></a>Question 1 - Basics and resources</h3><p>In this question, you create an Android app that displays your information according to the following requirements.</p><ul><li>The name of the app is “My Name”, and the package name of the app (i.e. app id)</li><li>By default, the app displays your name in English and your student ID.</li><li>If the locale of the device is traditional Chinese - Hong Kong, the app displays your name in Chinese and your student ID.<br>The following are sample outputs when the app is executed in locales of English (left) and traditional Chinese - Hong Kong (right), respectively.</li></ul><p>Submit one whole Android project that contains all your work for this question.</p><h3 id="Question-2-Layout-and-UI"><a href="#Question-2-Layout-and-UI" class="headerlink" title="Question 2 - Layout and UI"></a>Question 2 - Layout and UI</h3><p>Unit 6 contains an example app of a tip calculator. Enhance the app according to the following screenshots and requirements.</p><ul><li>a. Modify the portrait layout (existing in the project) to add 12 buttons under the “Bill Amount” input field, as shown in the left screenshot above.</li><li>b. Create a new landscape layout that contains the same components in the portrait layout (with the same IDs). Design the layout so that the components work properly in the landscape device orientation.</li><li>c. Implement the event handlers of the 12 new buttons as follows.</li><li>d. Create an “About” options menu item and show it as an action item. You may use a built-in Android drawable resource as its icon. When the item is selected, an “About” dialog box appears to show your name and your student ID, as in the middle screenshot above.</li><li>e. Create three options menu items “No fractional digits”, “One fractional digit”, and<br>“Two fractional digits”. These menu items are checkable, mutually exclusive, and in a group. They control the number of digits displayed after the decimal point for the output fields of “Total Bill Amount” and “Total Per Person”. The right screenshot above shows the output fields with one fractional digit.</li></ul><p>For simplicity, you may hard-code new strings in the programs, and don’t need to use primary or alternative string resources for them. Submit one whole Android project that contains all your work for this question.</p><h3 id="Question-3-Fragments-networking-and-concurrency"><a href="#Question-3-Fragments-networking-and-concurrency" class="headerlink" title="Question 3 - Fragments, networking and concurrency"></a>Question 3 - Fragments, networking and concurrency</h3><p>In this question, you develop an Android that checks the status of Web pages. A skeleton project, called WebChecker, is provided to you. Complete the project by working through the following tasks.</p><p>The following screenshots show the main screen (left) and log message screen (right) of the app. Submit one whole Android project that contains all your work for this question.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      完成一个Android应用程序，做一个小费计算器。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS5005-Sorting-Algorithms</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS5005-Sorting-Algorithms.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS5005-Sorting-Algorithms.html</id>
    <published>2022-09-01T09:27:04.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-09-01T09:28:23.908Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Discussion"><a href="#Discussion" class="headerlink" title="Discussion"></a>Discussion</h3><p>Sorting algorithms are arranging the given data in order. Several sorting techniques are used in almost every application to efficiently handle requests of many kinds. In this project, you would be implementing the Shell Sort and Adaptive sort techniques. You would also be measuring the time taken for each of them and plotting them as a line graph to visually compare.</p><h3 id="Implementation-of-the-class"><a href="#Implementation-of-the-class" class="headerlink" title="Implementation of the class"></a>Implementation of the class</h3><p>The sortData class defined in the sampleMainP3.cpp file will be used. The two fields we have here which are private are the number of elements(N) and the elements themselves(elements) which is an array of integers of either short or long(only for experimentation).<br>The methods(prototypes) that would be required for implementation of these sorting techniques are given to you in the sampleMain file.</p><h3 id="Generation-of-the-random-numbers-for-sorting"><a href="#Generation-of-the-random-numbers-for-sorting" class="headerlink" title="Generation of the random numbers for sorting"></a>Generation of the random numbers for sorting</h3><p>You are required to generate random numbers that are numElements number long. The numElements are given to you in the input file.<br>The way you would generate the random numbers is with the seed(srand()) that is given to you in the input file. This seed would make sure the random numbers that you generate are pseudo random. This means that with the same seed, every time you generate the numbers, it will be the same set of numbers.</p><p>The random numbers generated also need to be within the range(between lower and upper) given in the input file.<br>Input file<br>The first line in the input file is the number of elements(numElements). The line following that has the seed followed by the lower range and the upper range for random number generation.</p><h3 id="Submission"><a href="#Submission" class="headerlink" title="Submission"></a>Submission</h3><p>There will be 2 parts to the submission component in this project. To write the algorithms and sort the pseudo randomly generated numbers so that you pass the GradeScope autograding test cases(upload code saved as project4.cpp). The second would be to experiment and write a report on the sorting algorithms written for an array of short and long integers. More details follow.</p><h3 id="Autograder-submission"><a href="#Autograder-submission" class="headerlink" title="Autograder submission"></a>Autograder submission</h3><p>The code written for the autograding submission would be using the array of short integers. You are given a sample output file and you would need to write the algorithms and display the sorted numbers for the given input file. Nothing fancy here.</p><h3 id="Experimentation-and-Report-submission"><a href="#Experimentation-and-Report-submission" class="headerlink" title="Experimentation and Report submission"></a>Experimentation and Report submission</h3><p>For the experimentation part, you would change the class to having only the numElements and an array of long integers. And you would run both the sorting algorithms to sort these array of long integers.<br>You would have to plot the time taken for sorting(does not include random generation nor printing - use clock_t) 5000, 10000, 50000, 100000 number of elements for both short and long integers for both the algorithms(a graph(time vs numElements) with 4 lines).<br>You also need to explain the results you get by answering the question of why.</p><h3 id="Final-submission-requirement"><a href="#Final-submission-requirement" class="headerlink" title="Final submission requirement"></a>Final submission requirement</h3><p>You would need to submit 3 files at the end.</p><ol><li>project4.cpp - for autograding that uses array of short integers</li><li>project4_long.cpp - for review by grader and uses array of long integers</li><li>Report with plot.</li></ol><h3 id="Constraints"><a href="#Constraints" class="headerlink" title="Constraints"></a>Constraints</h3><ol><li>You are allowed to use only the libraries given in the sampleMainP4.cpp.</li><li>You need to work individually in this project.</li><li>Any use of internet’s resources need to be cited in your code.</li></ol>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      排序算法Sorting Algorithm按顺序排列给定的数据。几乎在每个应用程序中都使用了几种排序技术来有效处理多种请求。本次作业将实现Shell Sort和Adaptive sort算法，同时计算每个所花费的时间，并绘制为折线图以进行直观比较。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ECE175-Go-Fish</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/ECE175-Go-Fish.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/ECE175-Go-Fish.html</id>
    <published>2022-08-31T09:11:34.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-08-31T09:13:22.690Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>You are to develop an interactive game of Go Fish between two players. In Go Fish, each player takes turns asking for a card with a specific rank or face from another player. The goal is to form a book (a set of 4 cards with the same face or rank). The player with the most books at the end of the game is declared the winner. The gameplay for Go</p><p>Fish is described at <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_Fish" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_Fish</a>. Your program should operate as follows.</p><h3 id="Setup"><a href="#Setup" class="headerlink" title="Setup"></a>Setup</h3><p>Go Fish cards are represented as variables of the following type:</p><figure class="highlight cpp"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="keyword">typedef</span> <span class="class"><span class="keyword">struct</span> <span class="title">card_s</span> &#123;</span></span><br><span class="line">  <span class="keyword">char</span> suit[<span class="number">7</span>];</span><br><span class="line">  <span class="keyword">int</span> value;</span><br><span class="line">  <span class="class"><span class="keyword">struct</span> <span class="title">card_s</span> *<span class="title">pt</span>;</span></span><br><span class="line">&#125; card;</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><ol><li>You are allowed to add attributes to this definition, but not to remove any. You can represent colors by using card suits. Red: hearts; Yellow: diamonds; Green: clubs; Blue: spades. The action field is used to denote the function of action cards.</li><li>The game is played with a standard 52-card deck.</li><li>At the beginning, the user can choose to shuffle the deck or load a predefined sequence of cards from a file (for testing). The cards are stored in a file in a format of your choice. For instance, they could be stored in the form</li><li>The deck is implemented by a dynamic list of cards. This can be a singly-linked or a doubly-linked list (recommended). The cards drawn from the deck are deleted from the list.</li><li>Each player’s hand is implemented by a dynamic list of cards. The list is initially populated with the cards dealt to each player. The card drawn (played) by each player is added to (deleted from) the respective list.</li><li>The pool of cards in the center is implemented as a dynamic list of cards that is shuffled at the beginning of your game. The cards drawn or discarded in the pile is added/deleted in a dynamic fashion.</li></ol><h3 id="Game-Play"><a href="#Game-Play" class="headerlink" title="Game Play"></a>Game Play</h3><p>The gameplay is described at <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_Fish" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_Fish</a></p><h3 id="Optional-Features-for-Extra-Credit"><a href="#Optional-Features-for-Extra-Credit" class="headerlink" title="Optional Features for Extra Credit"></a>Optional Features for Extra Credit</h3><ol><li>Any number of players: Modify your code to work with more than two players. Look at the rule changes when more than 4 players participate (in terms of card dealing).</li><li>Game variations: Implement at least four game variations, as they are described in the game description.</li><li>Player automation: Automate one of the players to implement to play the game according to a winning strategy</li><li>Graphics. Add graphics to your game. You can print cards using ascii art. For example.</li></ol><h3 id="Sample-Execution"><a href="#Sample-Execution" class="headerlink" title="Sample Execution"></a>Sample Execution</h3><p>Note: You are encouraged to make your output look more appealing than what is given below. Your interface should display sufficient direction for a user to play the game. Get friends and family to play your game without much assistance.</p><p>It is very likely that you will not get the exact same code execution shown below. This is used to show you how the game should be played.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      代写游戏Go Fish，练习基本的C语言程序设计思想。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="C++" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/C/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Fundamentals" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Fundamentals/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CS12B-Edit-Distance</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS12B-Edit-Distance.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CS12B-Edit-Distance.html</id>
    <published>2022-08-31T08:40:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-08-31T08:43:13.452Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>You are to write a client program that computes the edit distance between two words, i.e., the minimum number of operations needed to transform one string into the other.</p><p>For this program, an operation is a substitution of as single character, such as from “brisk” to “brick”. The edit distance between the words “dog” and “cat” is 3, because the chain of “dot”, “cot” and “cat” transforms “dog” to “cat”.</p><p>When computing the edit distance between two words, each intermediate word must be an actual valid word. Edit distances are useful in applications that need to determine how similar two strings are, such as spelling checkers.</p><p>Your program should ask the user for the name of a dictionary text file (we will provide this). From this file, you should compute a map from every word to its intermediate neighbors; that is, the words that have an edit distance of 1 from it. Once this map is built, you can ask the user to enter two words to compare and you “walk” the map to find paths from one word to another. This process should be done in a loop: once you compute the edit distance of two words, you prompt again the user for the next two words.</p><p>A good way to process paths to walk the map is to use a linked list of words to visit, starting from the beginning word, such as “dog” in the above example. Your algorithm should repeatedly remove the front word of the list and add all of its neighbors to the end of the list, until the ending word (such as “cat”) is found or until the list becomes empty, which indicates that no path exists between the two words.</p><p>Special cases: (1) If a word is not included in the dictionary your program should print out the message “Word does not exist”, (2) The edit distance of two words with different length is not defined. Therefore, if the two words given as an input by the user do not have the same length then your program should print the message “No solution”, (3) if both cases (1) and (2) occur, you may print either error message.</p><h3 id="General-Guidelines"><a href="#General-Guidelines" class="headerlink" title="General Guidelines"></a>General Guidelines</h3><p>You should download from LATTE two dictionary files. File text.txt has a dictionary of 8 words. You can use it to the your program with the “dog”/“cat” example (among others). File dict.txt is a larger file and you should use it to test your program with more complex examples. We will be using this file for testing your programs.</p><p>You don’t need to create any classes for this part. You only need to write one client program and you should name it EditDistance.java. You should however break your program into methods (e.g., one that builds the map, show transformation paths, calculates edit distance, etc)</p><p>You will be graded on correctness and programming style including the use of good variable names, comments on each class and each method, using local variables when possible, correct use of generics and the other standard style guidelines.</p><h3 id="User-Interaction"><a href="#User-Interaction" class="headerlink" title="User Interaction:"></a>User Interaction:</h3><p>While you choose how you want to break your code up into methods, we choose how your program needs to behave externally. You must follow the template we outline for you below.</p><p>Your program should first ask the user for the name of a dictionary file on one line. Your program should then loop through the following interactions, each of which should be on a separate line.</p><p>Ask the user for two words separated by a single space for which to compute the edit distance.<br>Print “Path = “ followed by each word in the edit path (starting with the first word the user entered), a comma, a space, then the next word. A comma or a space should not follow the last word.<br>Print “Edit distance = x”, where x is the edit distance.<br>Here is an example user interaction where everything in bold is input by the user, and everything not in bold is output by your program.</p><figure class="highlight livecodeserver"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br><span class="line">8</span><br><span class="line">9</span><br><span class="line">10</span><br><span class="line">11</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">Enter name <span class="keyword">of</span> dictionary <span class="built_in">file</span>: dict.txt</span><br><span class="line">Enter <span class="literal">two</span> <span class="keyword">words</span> separated <span class="keyword">by</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="literal">space</span>: dog cat</span><br><span class="line">Path = dog, dot, cot, cat</span><br><span class="line">Edit distance = <span class="number">3</span></span><br><span class="line">Enter <span class="literal">two</span> <span class="keyword">words</span> separated <span class="keyword">by</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="literal">space</span>: brisk brick</span><br><span class="line">Path = brisk, brick</span><br><span class="line">Edit distance = <span class="number">1</span></span><br><span class="line">Enter <span class="literal">two</span> <span class="keyword">words</span> separated <span class="keyword">by</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="literal">space</span>: transportation cat</span><br><span class="line">No Solution</span><br><span class="line">Enter <span class="literal">two</span> <span class="keyword">words</span> separated <span class="keyword">by</span> <span class="keyword">a</span> <span class="literal">space</span>: foobar whobar</span><br><span class="line">Word does <span class="keyword">not</span> exist</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>You may choose to implement a quit operating by listening for a single word from the user, such as “quit”, if you would like, but you do not have to.</p><h3 id="Design-Hints"><a href="#Design-Hints" class="headerlink" title="Design Hints"></a>Design Hints</h3><p>There are better algorithms for computing edit distance, but this approach runs reasonably quickly even for a large dictionary like dict.txt. The slow part is computing the neighbors, but that could be pre-computed and stored in a separate file. The program uses a LinkedList as a queue to keep track of candidate words to explore. A set is used to keep track of previously explored words. The algorithm keeps a count of how many words are at each distance from the original word so that it can report the edit distance. It also constructs a map each time it explores that keeps track of how it got to each word. That allows the program to report the path between the two words. All in all, this involves a LOT of data structure manipulation using the standard Java collections classes.</p><p>You DON’T need to follow this design. You are free to design your own program as you wish.</p><h3 id="Submission"><a href="#Submission" class="headerlink" title="Submission"></a>Submission</h3><p>Your Java source code should be submitted via Latte the day it is due.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      根据题目所给的算法，计算单词之间的编辑距离。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Java" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/Java/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Data Structure" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Data-Structure/"/>
    
      <category term="Algorithm" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Algorithm/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>CSCI2110-Huffman-Coding</title>
    <link href="https://tk1307993.coding.me/CSCI2110-Huffman-Coding.html"/>
    <id>https://tk1307993.coding.me/CSCI2110-Huffman-Coding.html</id>
    <published>2022-08-31T08:17:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-08-31T08:21:02.809Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="Requirement"><a href="#Requirement" class="headerlink" title="Requirement"></a>Requirement</h3><p>The objective of this assignment is to implement the Huffman coding algorithm using the binary tree data structure.</p><p>Download BinaryTree.java, Frequency.txt and Pokemon.txt files given next to the Assignment link.</p><h3 id="Problem-Summary"><a href="#Problem-Summary" class="headerlink" title="Problem Summary"></a>Problem Summary</h3><p>You are given a table of letters of the English alphabet and their frequencies. Build a Huffman tree with the alphabet symbols and their probabilities. Derive the Huffman codes. Using the codes, encode a given text file with the codes. Decode the encoded text file and show that it is the same as the input text file.</p><h3 id="Problem-in-Detail"><a href="#Problem-in-Detail" class="headerlink" title="Problem in Detail"></a>Problem in Detail</h3><p>In order to help you with the assignment, here’s the Huffman algorithm step-by-step procedure (as discussed in the lectures).</p><h3 id="Step-1"><a href="#Step-1" class="headerlink" title="Step 1"></a>Step 1</h3><p>Read the text file frequency.txt. Its link is given next to this lab document. It contains the frequency of letters in the English alphabet based on a sample of 40,000 words as shown below. (The file actually contains each letter and its frequency on two separate lines).</p><p>To do this step, you will find it useful to create a class called Pair.java that defines the letter and its probability as an object.</p><figure class="highlight cpp"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br><span class="line">6</span><br><span class="line">7</span><br><span class="line">8</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="keyword">public</span> <span class="class"><span class="keyword">class</span> <span class="title">Pair</span> &#123;</span></span><br><span class="line">  <span class="keyword">private</span> <span class="keyword">char</span> letter;</span><br><span class="line">  <span class="keyword">private</span> <span class="keyword">double</span> prob;</span><br><span class="line"></span><br><span class="line">  <span class="comment">//constructor</span></span><br><span class="line">  <span class="comment">//get and set methods</span></span><br><span class="line">  <span class="comment">//toString method</span></span><br><span class="line">&#125;</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><h3 id="Step-2"><a href="#Step-2" class="headerlink" title="Step 2"></a>Step 2</h3><p>Using this set of letters and frequencies, build the Huffman tree.</p><h3 id="Step-3-1"><a href="#Step-3-1" class="headerlink" title="Step 3.1"></a>Step 3.1</h3><p>Create a queue of Binary Tree nodes. Each Binary Tree node is of type Pair. The queue can be implemented as another simple Arraylist, where enqueue means adding an item to the end of the Arraylist and dequeue means removing the item at index 0. That is, the queue is an Arraylist of type &lt;BinaryTree<pair>&gt;. The queue contains these sorted according to the increasing order of their frequencies. This is your Queue S. This is done by checking the Arraylist freqs for values in increasing order, creating the binary tree nodes and enqueueing them in the queue.</pair></p><p>If you enumerate the Queue S, it should have the Pair objects in increasing order of their frequencies</p><h3 id="Step-3-2"><a href="#Step-3-2" class="headerlink" title="Step 3.2"></a>Step 3.2</h3><p>Now initialize another queue T (another Arraylist) of type &lt;BinaryTree<pair>&gt;.</pair></p><h3 id="Step-3-3"><a href="#Step-3-3" class="headerlink" title="Step 3.3"></a>Step 3.3</h3><p>Build the Huffman tree according to the algorithm discussed in the lectures.</p><p>For instance, in the above example, first (‘Z’, 0.07) and (‘J’, 0.10), will be dequeued from S. Create a node with the combined frequency. What do you put as the character for the combined node? You can put a dummy character, say ‘&amp;’. So (‘&amp;’,0.17) will be the parent node, and (‘Z’, 0.07) and (‘J’, 0.10), will be the left and right children. This tree will be enqueued to Queue T.</p><p>Submit a zip file containing all the source codes (.java files), Frequency.txt, Pokemon.txt, Encoded.txt and Decoded.txt.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      使用Binary Tree代写Huffman Coding算法。
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Java" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/categories/Java/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Data Structure" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Data-Structure/"/>
    
      <category term="Algorithm" scheme="https://tk1307993.coding.me/tags/Algorithm/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
